which O
is O
2018 B-DATE
TAILLEFER B-PER
O I-PER
's O
work O
from O
Nestle B-ORG
S.A I-ORG
. I-ORG

search O
for O
St. B-ORG
John I-ORG
's I-ORG
University I-ORG
people O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Detroit I-ORG
Mercy I-ORG
expert O
conducting O
research O
on O
experimental B-KEY
result I-KEY

wan O
na O
find O
infsof B-CON
role B-KEY
Jackson B-PER
C I-PER
D I-PER
publications O
published O
by O
Kim B-PER
Younghye I-PER

show O
1948 B-DATE
journals O
which O
are O
published O
on O
ercimdl B-CON
made O
by O
G. B-PER
Loffler I-PER

which O
is O
kais B-CON
conceptual B-KEY
model I-KEY
1987 B-DATE
journal O
from O
Keene B-PER
Daniel I-PER
L I-PER
which O
is O
about O
computational B-KEY
method I-KEY

1942 B-DATE
iccd B-CON
papers O
which O
focus O
on O
dust B-KEY
by O
Izumi B-PER
Masayuki I-PER
from O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Verona I-ORG

people O
doing O
research O
on O
medical B-KEY
students I-KEY

is O
there O
Zhaozhao B-PER
Wang I-PER
's O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware I-ORG
publication O
that O
is O
made O
by O
Roche B-ORG
that O
is O
written O
by O
de B-PER
Paula I-PER
e I-PER
Silva I-PER
P I-PER
about O
intelligent B-KEY
control I-KEY

what O
are O
migration B-KEY
TRW B-ORG
scientists O
conducting O
research O
on O
value B-KEY

medical B-KEY
journals O
related O
to O
food B-KEY
safety I-KEY

find O
for O
preservation B-KEY
expert O

Northrop B-ORG
Grumman I-ORG
scientist O
from O
Cargill B-ORG

Fuxiang B-PER
Hou I-PER
papers O
written O
by O
S. B-PER
Marathe I-PER
that O
are O
done O
at O
1912 B-DATE
that O
are O
about O
goat B-KEY
appearing O
on O
jota B-CON

are O
there O
any O
protein-protein B-KEY
interaction I-KEY
Gordon B-PER
Stuart I-PER
R I-PER
1917 B-DATE
tse B-CON
publication O
written O
by O
Ken B-PER
Moore I-PER

search O
for O
conferences O

journals O
on O
path B-KEY

American B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Beirut I-ORG
professors O
who O
is O
at O
Microsoft B-ORG
doing O
research O
on O
Cobalt B-KEY

Infrared B-KEY
spectroscopy I-KEY
wcsp B-CON
Kai B-PER
Ling I-PER
publications O
published O
by O
Cowley B-PER
D I-PER
M I-PER
by O
Covance B-ORG
at O
1968 B-DATE

scientists O
conducting O
research O
on O
financing B-KEY

search O
for O
DMSO B-KEY
journal O

is O
there O
any O
developing B-KEY
countries I-KEY
journal O
that O
focus O
on O
heavy B-KEY
metals I-KEY

waim B-CON
J B-PER
Hamacher I-PER
Ruthenium B-KEY
researches O
done O
in O
1940 B-DATE
published O
on O
evoW B-CON
focusing O
on O
denoising B-KEY

what O
are O
complex B-KEY
network I-KEY
scientist O

2025 B-DATE
Montclair B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
dlog B-CON
publications O
which O
is O
published O
at O
1929 B-DATE

Atkinson B-PER
William I-PER
aaaiss B-CON
Influenza B-KEY
2007 B-DATE
journals O
related O
to O
stainless B-KEY
steel I-KEY
from O
CERN B-ORG
made O
by O
I B-PER
Langer I-PER
accepted O
by O
iasam B-CON
made O
at O
1933 B-DATE

people O
whose O
research O
is O
about O
alfalfa B-KEY
that O
work O
at O
Kaplan B-ORG
University I-ORG

tabu B-KEY
search I-KEY
expert O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Idaho I-ORG
researcher O

give O
me O
formal B-KEY
verification I-KEY
journals O
related O
to O
information B-KEY
processing I-KEY

what O
are O
researchers O
at O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wisconsin-Milwaukee I-ORG

show O
Transmission B-KEY
electron I-KEY
microscopy I-KEY
ESIC B-ORG
: I-ORG
Business I-ORG
& I-ORG
Marketing I-ORG
School I-ORG
journals O
that O
is O
by O
Hembree B-PER
Elizabeth I-PER
A I-PER
received O
by O
simulation B-CON

Electronic B-ORG
Data I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
cav B-CON
Li B-PER
Dapeng I-PER
's O
response B-KEY
time I-KEY
journal O
which O
are O
related O
to O
contract B-KEY

show O
R. B-PER
Dunkerley I-PER
color B-KEY
pimrc B-CON
journal O
that O
is O
written O
at O
2019 B-DATE
from O
Weatherford B-ORG
which O
are O
published O
on O
corr B-CON

Web B-KEY
journals O
that O
focus O
on O
Amygdala B-KEY

find O
for O
nitrite B-KEY
journal O

are O
there O
any O
hidden B-KEY
Markov I-KEY
model I-KEY
experts O
whose O
papers O
are O
about O
project B-KEY
management I-KEY

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Georgia I-ORG
experts O
doing O
Cerebellum B-KEY

are O
there O
Campbell B-ORG
University I-ORG
journals O
in O
2015 B-DATE

find O
the O
stress B-KEY
intensity I-KEY
factor I-KEY
conference O

Aston B-PER
J I-PER
W I-PER
1940 B-DATE
United B-ORG
Airlines I-ORG
papers O
in O
2006 B-DATE
published O
by O
YOSHIZUMI B-PER
M I-PER
related O
to O
proposed B-KEY
model I-KEY

wan O
na O
find O
the O
list O
of O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Central I-ORG
Arkansas I-ORG
denoising B-KEY
professor O

people O
whose O
works O
are O
related O
to O
trauma B-KEY
working O
at O
Universidad B-ORG
Politécnica I-ORG
de I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG

1928 B-DATE
sensor B-KEY
node I-KEY
ivc B-CON
paper O
published O
by O
Roberts B-PER
A I-PER
V I-PER
which O
is O
from O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Navarra I-ORG

2024 B-DATE
Zhidko B-PER
N I-PER
I I-PER
's O
Carbon B-KEY
work O
done O
at O
1919 B-DATE
written O
by O
US B-ORG
Air I-ORG
Force I-ORG

which O
are O
data B-KEY
envelopment I-KEY
analysis I-KEY
journals O
which O
are O
about O
Spine B-KEY

software B-CON
papers O
accepted O
by O
apweb B-CON

who O
are O
INSEAD B-ORG
professors O

wan O
na O
find O
researcher O
doing O
research O
on O
high B-KEY
accuracy I-KEY

OFDM B-KEY
conference O

want O
to O
find O
evaluation B-KEY
journals O
that O
is O
about O
comprehensive B-KEY
evaluation I-KEY

search O
the O
encryption B-KEY
Randstad B-ORG
expert O

School B-ORG
of I-ORG
Visual I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
expert O
doing O
research O
on O
New B-KEY
Zealand I-KEY

want O
to O
find O
Dallas B-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University I-ORG
O'Brien B-PER
Chris I-PER
's O
paper O
made O
in O
1977 B-DATE

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Birmingham I-ORG
NGF B-KEY
2018 B-DATE
journal O
made O
by O
Cassagneau B-PER
Romain I-PER
that O
are O
related O
to O
siRNA B-KEY
by O
Queens B-ORG
College I-ORG

show O
The B-ORG
Ohio I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
journal O
published O
by O
Skrzypczak B-PER
Jana I-PER
done O
at O
1911 B-DATE

cascon B-CON
research O
published O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
West I-ORG
Florida I-ORG

Sinnett B-PER
Daniel I-PER
Stanford B-ORG
University I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Medicine I-ORG
1914 B-DATE
work O
by O
UCLA B-ORG
written O
by O
Marchini B-PER
Cristina I-PER
which O
are O
at O
1912 B-DATE

give O
me O
a O
group O
of O
Charles B-ORG
Schwab I-ORG
pcs B-CON
2028 B-DATE
paper O
that O
is O
about O
course B-KEY
which O
is O
made O
by O
Verizon B-ORG
Business I-ORG
written O
by O
Kohler B-PER
, I-PER
W I-PER
. I-PER

conferences O

which O
is O
siamma B-CON
Progressive B-ORG
Insurance I-ORG
1943 B-DATE
paper O
that O
are O
accepted O
by O
jasis B-CON
done O
by O
Lingyun B-PER
Zou I-PER
written O
at O
1956 B-DATE
that O
focus O
on O
Ovarian B-KEY
cancer I-KEY

what O
are O
data B-KEY
envelopment I-KEY
analysis I-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Manitoba I-ORG
professors O

give O
me O
a O
group O
of O
explosion B-KEY
Charter B-ORG
Communications I-ORG
experts O

find O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Houston-Downtown I-ORG
1906 B-DATE
publication O
done O
by O
Fox B-PER
, I-PER
R.W I-PER
. I-PER
that O
are O
done O
in O
1930 B-DATE
written O
by O
Trinity B-ORG
University I-ORG

are O
there O
any O
metastasis B-KEY
conferences O

biological B-KEY
characteristics I-KEY
journal O
focusing O
on O
cat B-KEY

jsyml B-CON
Duke B-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
1980 B-DATE
works O
received O
by O
ires B-CON
that O
is O
done O
in O
2019 B-DATE
written O
by O
Searle B-PER
A I-PER
J I-PER
that O
is O
related O
to O
Chemiluminescence B-KEY
done O
by O
Deakin B-ORG
University I-ORG

pediatric B-KEY
professors O
conducting O
research O
on O
singularity B-KEY

comorbidity B-KEY
professor O
in O
Avery B-ORG
Dennison I-ORG

find O
for O
failure B-KEY
tcom B-CON
Scott B-PER
G I-PER
M I-PER
's O
work O
written O
at O
1989 B-DATE
accepted O
by O
ndjfl B-CON
by O
Wright B-PER
Patricia I-PER
A I-PER

give O
me O
researchers O
whose O
works O
is O
in O
process B-KEY
parameter I-KEY
at O
eBay B-ORG
Inc I-ORG

cost B-KEY
control I-KEY
conferences O

McCabe B-PER
J I-PER
B I-PER
's O
1954 B-DATE
edoc B-CON
paper O
made O
by O
de B-PER
la I-PER
Rosette I-PER
J I-PER
J I-PER
M I-PER
C I-PER
H I-PER

jat B-CON
2020 B-DATE
journals O
related O
to O
concanavalin B-KEY
A I-KEY

ANOVA B-KEY
publication O
that O
are O
related O
to O
therapeutic B-KEY
that O
is O
done O
at O
1907 B-DATE
that O
is O
published O
by O
Qiuhui B-PER
Chen I-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Louisville I-ORG
scientists O
at O
Yahoo B-ORG
! I-ORG

find O
a O
number O
of O
Universidad B-ORG
Autónoma I-ORG
de I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
Liver B-KEY
neoplasms I-KEY
experts O

who O
is O
people O

experimental B-KEY
result I-KEY
experts O
from O
Xi'an B-ORG
Jiaotong I-ORG
University I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
qualitative B-KEY
research I-KEY

are O
there O
journals O
appearing O
in O
icinco B-CON

find O
for O
the O
group O
of O
expert O
conducting O
research O
on O
iNOS B-KEY

Time B-ORG
Warner I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
experts O

search O
conferences O

asymmetric B-KEY
information I-KEY
journal O
on O
Prostate B-KEY
cancer I-KEY

conferences O
focusing O
on O
motivation B-KEY

find O
for O
Type B-KEY
2 I-KEY
diabetes I-KEY
professor O
doing O
research O
on O
PID B-KEY

which O
are O
jat B-CON
E B-PER
Meyer I-PER
Ca B-ORG
' I-ORG
Foscari I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Venice I-ORG
1946 B-DATE
disease B-KEY
journal O
made O
by O
ESADE B-ORG
Business I-ORG
& I-ORG
Law I-ORG
School I-ORG
on O
source B-KEY
code I-KEY
made O
by O
Chuanxian B-PER
Li I-PER
appearing O
in O
iciap B-CON

wan O
na O
find O
performance B-KEY
evaluation I-KEY
Lenovo B-ORG
researchers O
at O
The B-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
who O
is O
doing O
network B-KEY
environment I-KEY

journal O
related O
to O
identification B-KEY

experts O

Binghamton B-ORG
University I-ORG
Liver B-KEY
cirrhosis I-KEY
Mark B-PER
Gerber I-PER
's O
works O
by O
Xuebin B-PER
Wan I-PER
published O
at O
1992 B-DATE
from O
Technical B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Denmark I-ORG

Esophageal B-KEY
cancer I-KEY
scientist O
that O
are O
at O
SAIC B-ORG

are O
there O
any O
Gastric B-KEY
carcinoma I-KEY
researcher O
that O
is O
from O
University B-ORG
College I-ORG
Cork I-ORG

is O
there O
amcc B-CON
papers O
that O
is O
on O
tbc B-CON
done O
in O
1909 B-DATE
related O
to O
duality B-KEY

search O
the O
list O
of O
emulsion B-KEY
scientist O
working O
on O
Nicotine B-KEY

conferences O
related O
to O
environment B-KEY

researchers O
working O
on O
Drug B-KEY
delivery I-KEY

show O
the O
spl B-CON
Silano B-PER
Marco I-PER
1976 B-DATE
journals O
that O
is O
related O
to O
color B-KEY
image I-KEY
which O
are O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Massachusetts I-ORG
, I-ORG
Amherst I-ORG

system B-KEY
architecture I-KEY
scientists O
doing O
prostaglandin B-KEY
from O
Stony B-ORG
Brook I-ORG
University I-ORG

icnc B-CON
Insight B-ORG
Global I-ORG
researches O
by O
Suda B-PER
I I-PER
done O
in O
2004 B-DATE
written O
by O
Indiana B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Pennsylvania I-ORG

is O
there O
any O
researchers O
who O
is O
from O
Saatchi B-ORG
& I-ORG
Saatchi I-ORG
whose O
paper O
are O
about O
growth B-KEY
rate I-KEY

traditional B-KEY
culture I-KEY
Ernst B-ORG
& I-ORG
Young I-ORG
people O
whose O
papers O
are O
related O
to O
information B-KEY
theory I-KEY

sulfur B-KEY
1966 B-DATE
publications O
which O
are O
from O
Bank B-ORG
of I-ORG
China I-ORG
published O
at O
2023 B-DATE
written O
by O
Shah B-PER
V I-PER
D I-PER

who O
is O
peripheral B-KEY
blood I-KEY
mononuclear I-KEY
cells I-KEY
experts O
conducting O
research O
on O
shear B-KEY
strength I-KEY
at O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wollongong I-ORG

1984 B-DATE
noms B-CON
approach B-KEY
work O

what O
is O
cpc B-CON
Infection B-KEY
Chambers B-PER
F I-PER
A I-PER
's O
journals O
accepted O
by O
isi B-CON
written O
by O
Shad B-PER
Hazoor I-PER
A I-PER
which O
are O
about O
pattern B-KEY

is O
there O
tumor B-KEY
necrosis I-KEY
factor-alpha I-KEY
Vrije B-ORG
Universiteit I-ORG
Amsterdam I-ORG
1987 B-DATE
works O
related O
to O
object B-KEY
recognition I-KEY
published O
on O
www B-CON

what O
is O
1957 B-DATE
publication O
which O
are O
done O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Notre I-ORG
Dame I-ORG
that O
are O
written O
at O
1920 B-DATE
which O
is O
received O
by O
acm B-CON
published O
by O
Walls B-PER

silica B-KEY
City B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
San I-ORG
Francisco I-ORG
researcher O
at O
De B-ORG
Montfort I-ORG
University I-ORG

show O
the O
group O
of O
Universidade B-ORG
do I-ORG
Porto I-ORG
manufacturing B-KEY
experts O
doing O
flue-cured B-KEY
tobacco I-KEY

is O
there O
any O
ipmu B-CON
RIA B-KEY
1914 B-DATE
works O
which O
is O
made O
in O
1926 B-DATE
which O
are O
related O
to O
antioxidant B-KEY
activity I-KEY

journals O
that O
are O
related O
to O
Cell B-KEY
biology I-KEY

questionnaire B-KEY
conference O

is O
there O
1913 B-DATE
researches O
that O
appear O
on O
visualization B-CON

give O
me O
scientists O
doing O
multiagent B-KEY
system I-KEY

X-ray B-KEY
photoelectron I-KEY
spectroscopy I-KEY
professors O
working O
at O
Saint B-ORG
Louis I-ORG
University I-ORG

Teach B-ORG
For I-ORG
America I-ORG
expert O
from O
Walmart B-ORG

want O
to O
find O
a O
list O
of O
routing B-KEY
protocol I-KEY
journals O
related O
to O
data B-KEY
transmission I-KEY

is O
there O
Appalachian B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
experts O
that O
work O
in O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Groningen I-ORG

conference O
that O
focus O
on O
failure B-KEY

search O
for O
the O
group O
of O
Wong B-PER
B I-PER
A I-PER
publications O
on O
matrix B-KEY
published O
at O
1928 B-DATE
made O
by O
Xing B-PER
W I-PER

1994 B-DATE
Dabuxilatu B-PER
's O
Siemens B-ORG
paper O
written O
by O
Kim B-PER
Jong I-PER
Yeon I-PER
published O
by O
Istanbul B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG
related O
to O
hysteresis B-KEY

quality B-KEY
assurance I-KEY
conferences O

find O
philosophy B-KEY
robio B-CON
Universidade B-ORG
Católica I-ORG
Portuguesa I-ORG
1945 B-DATE
work O
done O
by O
PPG B-ORG
Industries I-ORG
made O
by O
Hou B-PER
Likun I-PER

are O
there O
sequence B-KEY
Shea B-PER
Patrick I-PER
J I-PER
work O
related O
to O
diarrhea B-KEY
written O
at O
1930 B-DATE

look O
up O
for O
iandc B-CON
2028 B-DATE
Pratt B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
publications O
made O
by O
M B-PER
Nelson I-PER
received O
by O
icdcsw B-CON
which O
are O
made O
in O
1952 B-DATE

Humphreys B-PER
J I-PER
E I-PER
1903 B-DATE
paper O
published O
on O
geoinformatics B-CON

anomaly B-KEY
detection I-KEY
expert O

search O
for O
2012 B-DATE
arachidonic B-KEY
acid I-KEY
journals O
written O
at O
1918 B-DATE

is O
there O
any O
Palamara B-PER
A I-PER
T I-PER
focs B-CON
1978 B-DATE
publication O
published O
on O
iccv B-CON
on O
particle B-KEY
swarm I-KEY
optimization I-KEY
made O
in O
2017 B-DATE

what O
is O
middleware B-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
West I-ORG
Florida I-ORG
expert O
in O
Accenture B-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Solutions I-ORG

experts O
from O
National B-ORG
Cheng I-ORG
Kung I-ORG
University I-ORG
doing O
research O
on O
Polyaniline B-KEY

periodic B-KEY
solution I-KEY
researchers O
working O
on O
DAB B-KEY

iccv B-CON
Hadas B-PER
, I-PER
Y I-PER
. I-PER
environment B-KEY
1975 B-DATE
journals O
in O
1955 B-DATE
written O
by O
A B-PER
Scardovi I-PER
which O
is O
on O
cata B-CON
written O
by O
Lloyds B-ORG
Banking I-ORG
Group I-ORG

accuracy B-KEY
kdd B-CON
Fluor B-ORG
research O
on O
monocytes B-KEY

Creighton B-ORG
University I-ORG
professor O
from O
Bain B-ORG
& I-ORG
Company I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
coating B-KEY

find O
for O
small B-KEY
number I-KEY
spaa B-CON
1994 B-DATE
work O
appearing O
in O
informs B-CON
that O
are O
written O
at O
1955 B-DATE
which O
are O
by O
Philadelphia B-ORG
University I-ORG

simulation B-KEY
model I-KEY
papers O
related O
to O
blood B-KEY
from O
N B-PER
Callaghan I-PER

which O
is O
adbis B-CON
Reid B-PER
H I-PER
M I-PER
publication O
focusing O
on O
conservation B-KEY
published O
in O
1919 B-DATE
appearing O
on O
tsg B-CON

are O
there O
numerical B-KEY
example I-KEY
conference O
focusing O
on O
Transcription B-KEY

search O
compgeom B-CON
Lewis B-ORG
University I-ORG
Horse B-KEY
research O
done O
by O
Uppsala B-ORG
University I-ORG
received O
by O
lics B-CON
focusing O
on O
content B-KEY
determination I-KEY

give O
me O
rationality B-KEY
experts O
from O
IBM B-ORG
Global I-ORG
Business I-ORG
Services I-ORG

query O
cisis B-CON
Yang B-PER
Chenlong I-PER
comparative B-KEY
study I-KEY
papers O
that O
focus O
on O
analytical B-KEY
model I-KEY
that O
is O
accepted O
by O
ijis B-CON

query O
the O
group O
of O
stiffness B-KEY
usenix B-CON
journals O
about O
nonlinear B-KEY
dynamics I-KEY

2025 B-DATE
efficient B-KEY
implementation I-KEY
Fujiyoshi B-PER
Akira I-PER
's O
paper O
that O
are O
on O
icra B-CON
done O
by O
Ramsey B-PER
Michael I-PER
H I-PER

search O
for O
a O
number O
of O
researchers O

find O
kinetic B-KEY
model I-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
South I-ORG
Carolina-Columbia I-ORG
researchers O
who O
are O
at O
Aflac B-ORG

is O
there O
any O
Sky B-ORG
Italia I-ORG
expert O
whose O
researches O
are O
related O
to O
Cardiomyocytes B-KEY

what O
are O
Norepinephrine B-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kent I-ORG
people O
working O
at O
Hays B-ORG
doing O
research O
on O
tomato B-KEY

conferences O
whose O
paper O
is O
in O
scattering B-KEY

expert O
in O
Southern B-ORG
Illinois I-ORG
University I-ORG
, I-ORG
Carbondale I-ORG

what O
are O
Adhesion B-KEY
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Defense I-ORG
scientist O

distance B-KEY
education I-KEY
cikm B-CON
Housset B-PER
P I-PER
's O
journals O
that O
are O
made O
at O
1974 B-DATE
which O
are O
by O
Martens B-PER
W I-PER

what O
are O
RadioShack B-ORG
market B-KEY
researchers O
doing O
tyrosine B-KEY
hydroxylase I-KEY

query O
computational B-KEY
model I-KEY
journals O
related O
to O
disability B-KEY

journal O

Fidelity B-ORG
Investments I-ORG
Piattelli B-PER
M I-PER
journals O
that O
are O
published O
in O
1976 B-DATE
published O
on O
icst B-CON

find O
for O
1951 B-DATE
leakage B-KEY
research O
made O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nebraska-Lincoln I-ORG
published O
at O
1946 B-DATE
from O
W. B-PER
Klaus I-PER

clrimg B-CON
1966 B-DATE
journal O
published O
on O
bmei B-CON
by O
Viacom B-ORG

what O
is O
scientist O
who O
work O
at O
Gap B-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
doing O
DSP B-KEY

conferences O
whose O
papers O
are O
related O
to O
protease B-KEY

image B-KEY
registration I-KEY
researchers O
working O
on O
Haloperidol B-KEY

is O
there O
any O
AstraZeneca B-ORG
compgeom B-CON
G B-KEY
protein-coupled I-KEY
receptor I-KEY
work O
written O
by O
R. B-PER
Cartier I-PER
about O
model B-KEY
test I-KEY
appearing O
in O
insk B-CON

Arthroscopy B-KEY
qip B-CON
publication O
written O
by O
Yamanoi B-PER
A I-PER
from O
Stevens B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

what O
is O
Capsaicin B-KEY
journals O
related O
to O
inspection B-KEY

who O
is O
scientist O
from O
Renault B-ORG

Lyapunov B-KEY
function I-KEY
Independent B-ORG
work O
related O
to O
virtual B-KEY
world I-KEY

search O
scientists O
who O
work O
at O
PetSmart B-ORG

1952 B-DATE
Holster B-PER
I I-PER
Lisanne I-PER
's O
high-rise B-KEY
building I-KEY
Gartner B-ORG
researches O
about O
Electron B-KEY

journal O
about O
Hydrogel B-KEY

Barton B-PER
I I-PER
G I-PER
's O
1932 B-DATE
works O
which O
is O
from O
NYC B-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Education I-ORG

which O
are O
conference O

is O
there O
any O
Wenqing B-PER
Yu I-PER
ivs B-CON
1930 B-DATE
work O
on O
complex B-KEY
system I-KEY

look O
up O
for O
Khursheed B-PER
N. I-PER
Jeejeebhoy I-PER
's O
stability B-KEY
analysis I-KEY
St. B-ORG
Mary I-ORG
's I-ORG
University I-ORG
work O

give O
me O
Prenatal B-KEY
diagnosis I-KEY
Kraft B-ORG
Foods I-ORG
Group I-ORG
professor O

Oxytocin B-KEY
1968 B-DATE
Prkacin B-PER
I I-PER
's O
papers O
related O
to O
Echocardiography B-KEY

find O
journal O
related O
to O
dissolution B-KEY

is O
there O
1910 B-DATE
Bampton B-PER
P I-PER
A I-PER
's O
papers O
accepted O
by O
isca B-CON
published O
at O
2027 B-DATE

germination B-KEY
professors O
working O
at O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kansas I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
diversity B-KEY

Northwestern B-ORG
Mutual I-ORG
dynamic B-KEY
model I-KEY
professors O

aspdac B-CON
publications O
by O
Macomb B-ORG
Community I-ORG
College I-ORG
which O
is O
published O
by O
G B-PER
Harrison I-PER

query O
some O
Cisco B-ORG
2027 B-DATE
work O
written O
by O
Hildebrandt B-PER
Niko I-PER
that O
is O
in O
1917 B-DATE

InterContinental B-ORG
Hotels I-ORG
Group I-ORG
OFDM B-KEY
cascon B-CON
1964 B-DATE
Koutsouris B-PER
D I-PER
's O
publication O
made O
in O
2027 B-DATE
focusing O
on O
conversion B-KEY
received O
by O
jcphy B-CON

conferences O
whose O
papers O
are O
in O
recognition B-KEY

give O
me O
Universidad B-ORG
Francisco I-ORG
de I-ORG
Vitoria I-ORG
scientist O
doing O
research O
on O
porosity B-KEY

are O
there O
fuin B-CON
Freescale B-ORG
Semiconductor I-ORG
Sophie B-PER
Ziegler I-PER
's O
cost B-KEY
control I-KEY
1978 B-DATE
research O
by O
Davis B-PER
Thomas I-PER
M I-PER
that O
appear O
on O
hmd B-CON
focusing O
on O
Cholecystectomy B-KEY

look O
up O
for O
jota B-CON
journal O
published O
on O
pcm B-CON
on O
prolactin B-KEY

are O
there O
any O
Independent B-ORG
Contractor I-ORG
experts O

query O
Teach B-ORG
for I-ORG
America I-ORG
scientist O
whose O
research O
is O
about O
correction B-KEY

give O
me O
Molybdenum B-KEY
conference O

uist B-CON
El B-PER
Hachem I-PER
May I-PER
's O
1937 B-DATE
publications O
by O
Labandeira B-PER
Javier I-PER

conferences O
on O
which O
the O
paper O
are O
about O
Antioxidant B-KEY
enzymes I-KEY

2020 B-DATE
pik B-CON
Naval B-ORG
Postgraduate I-ORG
School I-ORG
research O
that O
is O
related O
to O
convection B-KEY
made O
by O
Kispert B-PER
A I-PER
published O
in O
1974 B-DATE

find O
Xerox B-ORG
expert O
from O
Ca B-ORG
' I-ORG
Foscari I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Venice I-ORG

Army B-ORG
National I-ORG
Guard I-ORG
Matthew B-PER
Brenner I-PER
bmvc B-CON
work O
made O
in O
1964 B-DATE
that O
are O
about O
Crosslinking B-KEY

is O
there O
www B-CON
West B-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
University I-ORG
2029 B-DATE
Timoshin B-PER
A I-PER
D I-PER
's O
research O
about O
MEMS B-KEY
that O
are O
published O
by O
Cintas B-ORG
on O
jifs B-CON

Saudi B-ORG
Aramco I-ORG
people O
at O
Grant B-ORG
Thornton I-ORG
LLP I-ORG

want O
to O
find O
those O
Hemodialysis B-KEY
conference O
of O
which O
the O
papers O
focus O
on O
singularity B-KEY

aciids B-CON
Duke B-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
1912 B-DATE
work O
by O
Walgreens B-ORG
published O
by O
Fansheng B-PER
Ceng I-PER
on O
isr B-CON
that O
is O
at O
1919 B-DATE

journals O

Ain B-ORG
Shams I-ORG
University I-ORG
professor O
who O
is O
in O
TOTAL B-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
Research B-KEY
Articles I-KEY

want O
to O
find O
those O
professors O

search O
conferences O
on O
high-density B-KEY
lipoprotein I-KEY

pretreatment B-KEY
experts O
whose O
work O
are O
in O
surface B-KEY
modification I-KEY

Autónomo B-ORG
professors O

research B-KEY
Chase B-ORG
scientists O
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Missouri I-ORG

which O
is O
issac B-CON
1931 B-DATE
works O
made O
by O
Progressive B-ORG
Insurance I-ORG
written O
at O
1951 B-DATE
accepted O
by O
eaai B-CON

winter B-KEY
wheat I-KEY
journal O

The B-ORG
Dow I-ORG
Chemical I-ORG
Company I-ORG
Clarke B-PER
J I-PER
O I-PER
acoustic B-KEY
emission I-KEY
publications O
by O
Tsitsiklis B-PER
, I-PER
J.N I-PER
. I-PER
published O
at O
2018 B-DATE

core B-KEY
scientist O

Bombardier B-ORG
Transportation I-ORG
reading B-KEY
people O
working O
at O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Portsmouth I-ORG

Caterpillar B-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
researcher O
working O
on O
Parkinson B-KEY
's I-KEY
disease I-KEY

constitution B-KEY
experts O
working O
at O
Convergys B-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
remote B-KEY
monitoring I-KEY

journals O

what O
is O
conference O
related O
to O
coupling B-KEY

find O
Pontificia B-ORG
Universidad I-ORG
Católica I-ORG
de I-ORG
Chile I-ORG
wavelet B-KEY
analysis I-KEY
people O
working O
at O
Janssen B-ORG
, I-ORG
Pharmaceutical I-ORG
Companies I-ORG
of I-ORG
Johnson I-ORG
and I-ORG
Johnson I-ORG
doing O
research O
on O
Preeclampsia B-KEY

is O
there O
1991 B-DATE
ismvl B-CON
glutathione B-KEY
S I-KEY
-transferase I-KEY
works O
published O
by O
Carr B-PER
I I-PER
C I-PER
appearing O
in O
expert B-CON

conference O
on O
MEMS B-KEY

is O
there O
any O
Katholieke B-ORG
Universiteit I-ORG
Leuven I-ORG
1982 B-DATE
Kooiker B-PER
Maarten I-PER
's O
bioinformatics B-CON
phytoplankton B-KEY
papers O
appearing O
on O
wetice B-CON
that O
is O
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
California I-ORG
which O
are O
done O
in O
1910 B-DATE

liquid B-KEY
crystal I-KEY
researches O
written O
by O
Jadavpur B-ORG
University I-ORG
published O
in O
1962 B-DATE
made O
by O
Chaoguang B-PER
Wang I-PER

methotrexate B-KEY
1988 B-DATE
La B-ORG
Salle I-ORG
University I-ORG
journals O
appearing O
on O
wetice B-CON

performance B-KEY
model I-KEY
sofsem B-CON
Paul B-PER
Ian I-PER
M I-PER
's O
1922 B-DATE
work O
done O
by O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Genova I-ORG
that O
are O
at O
2018 B-DATE

Texas B-ORG
Woman I-ORG
's I-ORG
University I-ORG
McCall B-PER
John I-PER
L I-PER
surface B-KEY
modification I-KEY
1945 B-DATE
publications O
which O
are O
made O
at O
1996 B-DATE
which O
are O
written O
by O
Changsheng B-PER
Du I-PER
which O
is O
related O
to O
cytoskeleton B-KEY

Peide B-PER
Li I-PER
La B-ORG
Salle I-ORG
University I-ORG
journal O
written O
by O
Istanbul B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG

Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Pavia I-ORG
scientist O
working O
at O
Queen B-ORG
Mary I-ORG
, I-ORG
U. I-ORG
of I-ORG
London I-ORG

find O
for O
fatty B-KEY
acids I-KEY
Hartmut B-PER
Kern I-PER
's O
visapp B-CON
2002 B-DATE
journals O
received O
by O
flairs B-CON
from O
Benedictine B-ORG
University I-ORG
related O
to O
base B-KEY
station I-KEY

show O
research B-KEY
CNRS B-ORG
journal O
written O
at O
1971 B-DATE
written O
by O
Linda B-PER
Charles I-PER
related O
to O
control B-KEY
measures I-KEY
made O
by O
Universidad B-ORG
Nacional I-ORG
de I-ORG
Colombia I-ORG

what O
are O
1981 B-DATE
I.S B-PER
. I-PER
Cooper I-PER
's O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
publications O
made O
by O
Manhattan B-ORG
College I-ORG
done O
at O
2027 B-DATE
done O
by O
Yongxiang B-PER
Lu I-PER

Rheology B-KEY
journals O
focusing O
on O
USA B-KEY

are O
there O
any O
prostaglandin B-KEY
American B-ORG
Eagle I-ORG
Outfitters I-ORG
professor O
conducting O
research O
on O
teacher B-KEY
at O
Clark B-ORG
University I-ORG

want O
to O
find O
journal O
focusing O
on O
fluoride B-KEY

GERHARDT B-PER
P I-PER
R I-PER
CenturyLink B-ORG
1984 B-DATE
journal O
by O
Columbia B-ORG
College I-ORG
Chicago I-ORG
that O
are O
by O
Henig B-PER
A I-PER

1923 B-DATE
Simon B-ORG
Fraser I-ORG
University I-ORG
journal O
which O
are O
done O
in O
1915 B-DATE
done O
by O
J. B-PER
Bredow I-PER
that O
are O
by O
Danmarks B-ORG
Tekniske I-ORG
Universitet I-ORG
which O
is O
about O
Web B-KEY
site I-KEY

Fairleigh B-ORG
Dickinson I-ORG
University I-ORG
Yabo B-PER
Liu I-PER
's O
jsac B-CON
journals O
done O
in O
1938 B-DATE
made O
by O
Lejeune B-PER
F I-PER
J I-PER
on O
ipccc B-CON

X-ray B-KEY
researchers O
doing O
internationalization B-KEY
from O
Western B-ORG
Illinois I-ORG
University I-ORG

what O
are O
Deloitte B-ORG
& I-ORG
Touche I-ORG
Liu B-PER
Shusen I-PER
1951 B-DATE
journal O
which O
appear O
on O
cssc B-CON
done O
at O
2002 B-DATE

is O
there O
high-density B-KEY
lipoprotein I-KEY
journals O

Human B-KEY
professors O

jpdc B-CON
work O
about O
design B-KEY
principle I-KEY
written O
by O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Granada I-ORG

wan O
na O
find O
journal O

are O
there O
1956 B-DATE
Lavoratore B-ORG
autonomo I-ORG
works O
written O
in O
1915 B-DATE
which O
are O
related O
to O
iterative B-KEY
algorithm I-KEY
made O
by O
BROWN B-PER
B I-PER

Hong B-KEY
Kong I-KEY
Messmer B-PER
Bruno I-PER
J I-PER
's O
publication O
which O
is O
published O
in O
1985 B-DATE
accepted O
by O
cvgip B-CON

is O
there O
knowledge B-KEY
researcher O
from O
HCL B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
working O
on O
Calorimetry B-KEY

conference O

show O
integer B-KEY
programming I-KEY
papers O
on O
graph B-KEY
G I-KEY
published O
in O
2002 B-DATE
which O
is O
on O
rtss B-CON

which O
are O
Université B-ORG
catholique I-ORG
de I-ORG
Louvain I-ORG
1993 B-DATE
research O
made O
by O
Diachuk B-PER
V I-PER
V I-PER
published O
by O
Islamic B-ORG
Azad I-ORG
University I-ORG
focusing O
on O
algorithm B-KEY
written O
at O
1971 B-DATE

virtual B-KEY
prototype I-KEY
experts O

endoplasmic B-KEY
reticulum I-KEY
scientist O
at O
Dallas B-ORG
Baptist I-ORG
University I-ORG

Hypothalamus B-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maine I-ORG
professors O
who O
are O
from O
Procter B-ORG
& I-ORG
Gamble I-ORG
working O
on O
heart B-KEY
rate I-KEY
variability I-KEY

expert O
that O
is O
from O
BBVA B-ORG
who O
are O
doing O
chicken B-KEY

who O
is O
PAH B-KEY
researchers O

search O
prototype B-KEY
system I-KEY
conference O

wan O
na O
find O
Shibata B-PER
Hiroyuki I-PER
's O
work O
received O
by O
isscc B-CON
made O
by O
Guţiu B-PER
I I-PER

supply B-KEY
chain I-KEY
researchers O
who O
do O
circulation B-KEY
at O
The B-ORG
Citadel I-ORG

what O
are O
expert O
whose O
work O
is O
in O
New B-KEY
Zealand I-KEY

find O
a O
list O
of O
scientists O
at O
St B-ORG
. I-ORG
Cloud I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG

Cirrhosis B-KEY
scientists O
whose O
work O
is O
about O
genetic B-KEY
diversity I-KEY

X-ray B-KEY
diffraction I-KEY
Sijbrands B-PER
E I-PER
J I-PER
eurocast B-CON
Comcast B-ORG
research O
which O
are O
done O
by O
J. B-PER
Bala I-PER
appearing O
on O
iacr B-CON

scientist O
who O
is O
doing O
research O
on O
MEMS B-KEY

wan O
na O
find O
Weinger B-PER
Jason I-PER
G I-PER
's O
paper O
received O
by O
ACMace B-CON
made O
by O
Kuipers B-PER
Jeroen I-PER
at O
1980 B-DATE

construction B-KEY
project I-KEY
conference O

look O
up O
for O
experts O
whose O
researches O
focus O
on O
Addiction B-KEY

C B-PER
Philips I-PER
tvt B-CON
researches O
received O
by O
sigmetrics B-CON
made O
by O
SunTrust B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
focusing O
on O
previous B-KEY
work I-KEY

journals O
which O
focus O
on O
microsatellite B-KEY

biological B-KEY
control I-KEY
conferences O

give O
me O
the O
list O
of O
salesforce.com B-ORG
1910 B-DATE
papers O
that O
are O
written O
in O
1999 B-DATE
done O
by O
Delta B-ORG
Air I-ORG
Lines I-ORG

research O
published O
at O
1995 B-DATE
by O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Bergamo I-ORG

give O
me O
signal-to-noise B-KEY
ratio I-KEY
geb B-CON
1904 B-DATE
paper O
appearing O
in O
ecoop B-CON
published O
at O
1917 B-DATE
from O
Haigh B-PER
W I-PER
G I-PER
that O
focus O
on O
persistence B-KEY

radiation B-KEY
scientist O

Fiserv B-ORG
researchers O

search O
for O
Symantec B-ORG
professor O
at O
Fresenius B-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Care I-ORG

wan O
na O
find O
electrolyte B-KEY
conferences O

icis B-CON
1913 B-DATE
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Akron I-ORG
Golovistikov B-PER
I I-PER
N I-PER
publication O
made O
by O
Kendriya B-ORG
Vidyalaya I-ORG
that O
focus O
on O
Epstein-Barr B-KEY
virus I-KEY
that O
is O
on O
cad B-CON

are O
there O
people O
conducting O
research O
on O
Complications B-KEY

who O
are O
expert O
conducting O
research O
on O
Hepatitis B-KEY

EMC B-ORG
horizontal B-KEY
well I-KEY
experts O

find O
for O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Alcalá I-ORG
scientist O
working O
on O
ACE B-KEY
from O
Universidade B-ORG
Estadual I-ORG
de I-ORG
Campinas I-ORG

wan O
na O
find O
a O
number O
of O
investment B-KEY
researchers O
that O
are O
working O
on O
phase B-KEY
transition I-KEY
at O
Teach B-ORG
For I-ORG
America I-ORG

is O
there O
General B-ORG
Motors I-ORG
scientists O
working O
at O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Bari I-ORG

2004 B-DATE
Food B-KEY
intake I-KEY
geb B-CON
publications O
received O
by O
csee B-CON
at O
1902 B-DATE
published O
by O
Keith B-PER
Robinson I-PER
focusing O
on O
membership B-KEY
function I-KEY

Guizhou B-KEY
experts O
doing O
research O
on O
Cobalt B-KEY

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Padova I-ORG
professors O
doing O
research O
on O
vulnerability B-KEY

jphil B-CON
Visvesvaraya B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University I-ORG
2013 B-DATE
Lepping B-PER
Peter I-PER
publications O
made O
at O
1939 B-DATE
accepted O
by O
monet B-CON
published O
by O
Lucent B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
which O
is O
about O
collagen B-KEY

is O
there O
Electronic B-ORG
Data I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
experts O
working O
on O
virtual B-KEY
machine I-KEY

Breast B-KEY
Eastern B-ORG
Kentucky I-ORG
University I-ORG
researcher O

want O
to O
find O
RABAEY B-PER
M I-PER
1909 B-DATE
idea B-KEY
works O
made O
at O
1922 B-DATE
written O
by O
Alstom B-ORG
Power I-ORG

search O
for O
a O
group O
of O
1916 B-DATE
Lehman B-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
electrophoresis B-KEY
researches O
related O
to O
water B-KEY
use I-KEY
efficiency I-KEY
which O
are O
made O
at O
1918 B-DATE
published O
by O
Maoyue B-PER
Li I-PER

want O
to O
find O
2019 B-DATE
Mian B-PER
Lu I-PER
's O
research O
from O
TIAA-CREF B-ORG
published O
at O
1931 B-DATE

are O
there O
any O
Norwich B-ORG
University I-ORG
people O
working O
at O
Kaplan B-ORG
University I-ORG

search O
conference O

is O
there O
1963 B-DATE
winet B-CON
optimization B-KEY
algorithm I-KEY
Kuan B-PER
Chen I-PER
research O
on O
tim B-CON
which O
is O
about O
proposed B-KEY
approach I-KEY

Universitat B-ORG
de I-ORG
Girona I-ORG
experts O
working O
at O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Victoria I-ORG
who O
work O
on O
breast B-KEY
cancer I-KEY

1981 B-DATE
phenol B-KEY
publication O
related O
to O
solution B-KEY

In B-KEY
situ I-KEY
hybridization I-KEY
Idaho B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
researchers O
who O
are O
working O
on O
particle B-KEY
swarm I-KEY
optimization I-KEY
at O
Bradley B-ORG
University I-ORG

Davison B-PER
Joyce I-PER
's O
Northrop B-ORG
Grumman I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
ijon B-CON
data B-KEY
envelopment I-KEY
analysis I-KEY
papers O
received O
by O
focs B-CON

SWOT B-KEY
analysis I-KEY
Northwestern B-ORG
Mutual I-ORG
researchers O
doing O
research O
on O
staging B-KEY

which O
is O
pvldb B-CON
Mashima B-PER
Hirosato I-PER
's O
Cobalt B-KEY
Thomson B-ORG
Reuters I-ORG
research O
made O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Bridgeport I-ORG
written O
at O
1946 B-DATE
which O
are O
about O
Helicobacter B-KEY
pylori I-KEY
published O
on O
hpcc B-CON

competition B-KEY
1915 B-DATE
journals O
about O
health B-KEY
written O
by O
Amgen B-ORG
done O
by O
Dewing B-PER
J I-PER

water B-KEY
stress I-KEY
people O

sustainable B-KEY
development I-KEY
conference O

show O
the O
list O
of O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Birmingham I-ORG
1920 B-DATE
γ-aminobutyric B-KEY
acid I-KEY
researches O
by O
McGladrey B-ORG

U.S. B-ORG
Coast I-ORG
Guard I-ORG
expert O
whose O
work O
are O
about O
Manipulation B-KEY

look O
up O
for O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leeds I-ORG
Vander B-PER
Borght I-PER
Sara I-PER
publication O
done O
by O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Navy I-ORG
from O
Caprio B-PER
G I-PER

is O
there O
Pepperdine B-ORG
University I-ORG
1989 B-DATE
jet B-CON
journal O
written O
at O
1928 B-DATE
that O
are O
made O
by O
Universidad B-ORG
Europea I-ORG
de I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
related O
to O
graph B-KEY
that O
appear O
in O
rtss B-CON

are O
there O
Barry B-ORG
University I-ORG
researchers O

isspa B-CON
1957 B-DATE
work O
about O
Histamine B-KEY
published O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Maryland I-ORG
College I-ORG
Park I-ORG

STMicroelectronics B-ORG
large B-KEY
number I-KEY
journals O
focusing O
on O
Shanghai B-KEY
made O
at O
1977 B-DATE
by O
Shardonofsky B-PER
F I-PER
R I-PER

journal O

search O
for O
DMSO B-KEY
researchers O

EDF B-ORG
DeKosky B-PER
S I-PER
T I-PER
1981 B-DATE
publication O
which O
are O
written O
at O
1978 B-DATE
made O
by O
Saklani B-PER
Avanish I-PER
published O
on O
iciar B-CON

is O
there O
any O
Humber B-ORG
College I-ORG
experts O
working O
at O
Occidental B-ORG
College I-ORG
whose O
papers O
focus O
on O
MDA B-KEY

The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Manchester I-ORG
problem B-KEY
researchers O
conducting O
research O
on O
PAGE B-KEY

is O
there O
A. B-PER
Meiri I-PER
tgrs B-CON
papers O
that O
is O
by O
Universidad B-ORG
Iberoamericana I-ORG
, I-ORG
Ciudad I-ORG
de I-ORG
México I-ORG
which O
are O
related O
to O
process B-KEY
model I-KEY
published O
by O
Rajtar B-PER
Barbara I-PER
which O
is O
in O
1977 B-DATE
received O
by O
jvcir B-CON

is O
there O
evaluation B-KEY
system I-KEY
professors O
in O
UCSD B-ORG
doing O
activity B-KEY

what O
is O
researchers O
that O
are O
in O
Subway B-ORG
doing O
research O
on O
barley B-KEY

search O
Mass B-KEY
spectrometry I-KEY
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Los I-ORG
Andes I-ORG
scientists O
who O
work O
in O
Old B-ORG
Dominion I-ORG
University I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
Middle B-KEY
Age I-KEY

show O
London B-ORG
South I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
University I-ORG
Bo B-PER
Shen I-PER
paper O
which O
is O
published O
in O
2007 B-DATE
published O
by O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Cagliari I-ORG
done O
by O
Bertucci B-PER
R I-PER
related O
to O
diarrhea B-KEY

journal O
focusing O
on O
prostate B-KEY
specific I-KEY
antigen I-KEY

are O
there O
any O
scientists O
who O
are O
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
South I-ORG
Australia I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
Gastric B-KEY
cancer I-KEY

are O
there O
Transmission B-KEY
electron I-KEY
microscopy I-KEY
experts O

sol-gel B-KEY
scientist O
working O
on O
semantics B-KEY
in O
California B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

what O
are O
jpdc B-CON
journals O
which O
is O
made O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aberdeen I-ORG
related O
to O
total B-KEY
flavonoids I-KEY

new B-KEY
record I-KEY
conference O
which O
are O
about O
correlation B-KEY
coefficient I-KEY

Marshall B-ORG
University I-ORG
professors O
from O
National B-ORG
Chiao I-ORG
Tung I-ORG
University I-ORG
working O
on O
flow B-KEY

journals O

is O
there O
any O
Iona B-ORG
College I-ORG
coordination B-KEY
bioinformatics B-CON
Vinogradov B-PER
A I-PER
A I-PER
research O
by O
Texas B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
that O
are O
related O
to O
carotenoids B-KEY

experts O
from O
Telecom B-ORG
Italia I-ORG
that O
work O
on O
microwave B-KEY

what O
are O
Spinella B-PER
D I-PER
G I-PER
aspdac B-CON
ACh B-KEY
2002 B-DATE
research O
published O
on O
adt B-CON
that O
is O
at O
1947 B-DATE
related O
to O
steroids B-KEY

intrusion B-KEY
detection I-KEY
system I-KEY
journals O

Self B-ORG
employed I-ORG
ismir B-CON
1956 B-DATE
teaching B-KEY
journal O
by O
Holmes B-PER
K I-PER
M I-PER
that O
appear O
on O
icc B-CON

which O
is O
acm B-CON
erythropoietin B-KEY
researches O
which O
are O
published O
by O
Shouyun B-PER
Shen I-PER
which O
is O
about O
green B-KEY
fluorescent I-KEY
protein I-KEY

is O
there O
phase B-KEY
transition I-KEY
Universidade B-ORG
de I-ORG
São I-ORG
Paulo I-ORG
Pederson B-PER
William I-PER
C I-PER
1989 B-DATE
research O

kinetics B-KEY
Delft B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
journals O
made O
by O
Glazer B-PER
J I-PER
P I-PER
published O
at O
2024 B-DATE

sigecom B-CON
toxicity B-KEY
1965 B-DATE
works O
focusing O
on O
ubiquitin B-KEY
by O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
College I-ORG
at I-ORG
Buffalo I-ORG
made O
by O
Xinwen B-PER
Xu I-PER

which O
are O
E. B-KEY
coli I-KEY
qip B-CON
Xuxia B-PER
Liu I-PER
's O
paper O
in O
1912 B-DATE
appearing O
on O
pami B-CON
done O
by O
Austin B-ORG
Community I-ORG
College I-ORG

find O
for O
monkey B-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
San I-ORG
Diego I-ORG
researcher O
working O
at O
Scotiabank B-ORG
working O
on O
Henan B-KEY
Province I-KEY

look O
up O
for O
Tangermann B-PER
R I-PER
H I-PER
's O
geb B-CON
Arthur B-ORG
Andersen I-ORG
journals O
published O
on O
icnsc B-CON

give O
me O
Illinois B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
scientists O
at O
The B-ORG
Walt I-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Company I-ORG

search O
for O
Malasao B-PER
Rungnapa I-PER
's O
kdd B-CON
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
North I-ORG
Texas I-ORG
work O
that O
are O
from O
Valeo B-ORG
appearing O
on O
soco B-CON

look O
up O
for O
variability B-KEY
icis B-CON
Suzuki B-PER
Ayako I-PER
's O
journal O
received O
by O
icml B-CON
which O
are O
related O
to O
graphical B-KEY
user I-KEY
interface I-KEY
that O
are O
written O
by O
UnitedHealth B-ORG
Group I-ORG
done O
at O
2006 B-DATE

search O
for O
Conture B-PER
E I-PER
G I-PER
1989 B-DATE
publications O
on O
corr B-CON
about O
flue-cured B-KEY
tobacco I-KEY

is O
there O
Novartis B-ORG
researchers O
that O
work O
on O
pragmatics B-KEY

search O
for O
practice B-KEY
teaching I-KEY
professor O
from O
Wyeth B-ORG
who O
are O
working O
on O
informatization B-KEY

Insulin B-KEY
resistance I-KEY
Universidade B-ORG
Estadual I-ORG
de I-ORG
Campinas I-ORG
expert O

look O
up O
for O
1986 B-DATE
cicc B-CON
growth B-KEY
and I-KEY
development I-KEY
researches O
written O
by O
SCHWIMMER B-PER
S I-PER

Lawrence B-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University I-ORG
cmg B-CON
research O
which O
is O
done O
in O
1913 B-DATE
related O
to O
carbohydrates B-KEY
by O
Fang B-PER
Fang I-PER
which O
is O
done O
by O
Enterprise B-ORG
Rent-A-Car I-ORG

journals O
about O
radiation B-KEY

transition B-KEY
2026 B-DATE
Rychnovsky B-PER
Scott I-PER
D I-PER
researches O
about O
Radiotherapy B-KEY
written O
by O
Guanghua B-PER
Fan I-PER
done O
by O
London B-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
University I-ORG

what O
is O
tmi B-CON
1983 B-DATE
research O
which O
focus O
on O
HDL B-KEY
which O
is O
by O
LG B-ORG
Electronics I-ORG

is O
there O
any O
ijcomsys B-CON
1947 B-DATE
Saint B-ORG
Joseph I-ORG
's I-ORG
University I-ORG
publications O
appearing O
in O
siamnum B-CON
by O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Connecticut I-ORG
by O
N B-PER
Chandra I-PER

search O
Event-related B-KEY
potentials I-KEY
experts O
working O
on O
insect B-KEY

wpc B-CON
characterization B-KEY
papers O
received O
by O
dagstuhl B-CON
at O
1999 B-DATE

N B-KEY
-methyl- I-KEY
d I-KEY
-aspartate I-KEY
professors O

search O
Motorola B-ORG
Solutions I-ORG
Ralston B-PER
J I-PER
papers O
which O
are O
about O
electromagnetic B-KEY
field I-KEY
published O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California I-ORG
, I-ORG
Berkeley I-ORG
- I-ORG
Walter I-ORG
A. I-ORG
Haas I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Business I-ORG

is O
there O
Syracuse B-ORG
University I-ORG
proposed B-KEY
algorithm I-KEY
experts O

Shibib B-PER
, I-PER
M.A I-PER
. I-PER
's O
CNS B-KEY
1951 B-DATE
itiis B-CON
work O
about O
Scanning B-KEY
electron I-KEY
microscopy I-KEY
received O
by O
icassp B-CON

conference O

what O
are O
classification B-KEY
experts O

find O
for O
a O
number O
of O
1908 B-DATE
work O
by O
A. B-PER
Maréchal I-PER
from O
Capgemini B-ORG

is O
there O
Type B-KEY
2 I-KEY
diabetes I-KEY
mellitus I-KEY
conference O
on O
extraction B-KEY

is O
there O
Texas B-ORG
A I-ORG
& I-ORG
M I-ORG
University-Commerce I-ORG
expert O

find O
a O
group O
of O
1998 B-DATE
Aspirin B-KEY
fedcsis B-CON
works O
focusing O
on O
numerical B-KEY
method I-KEY
from O
TIAA-CREF B-ORG

professors O
at O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Baltimore I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
Diamond B-KEY

researchers O

supply B-KEY
chain I-KEY
management I-KEY
computing B-CON
1970 B-DATE
journal O
by O
Michael B-ORG
Page I-ORG
from O
B B-PER
Rajan I-PER
related O
to O
polarization B-KEY
appearing O
on O
spl B-CON

is O
there O
1951 B-DATE
ijmms B-CON
water B-KEY
Simmons B-ORG
College I-ORG
publications O
that O
is O
accepted O
by O
cgf B-CON

researchers O
conducting O
research O
on O
Mammals B-KEY

search O
for O
immunoglobulin B-KEY
journals O

which O
are O
index B-KEY
journals O
about O
refinement B-KEY

is O
there O
any O
1945 B-DATE
robot B-KEY
sitis B-CON
paper O
related O
to O
heuristics B-KEY
published O
by O
Sony B-ORG

find O
for O
the O
group O
of O
iam B-CON
HSBC B-ORG
1938 B-DATE
publications O
on O
potassium B-KEY
done O
by O
Florida B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
that O
are O
on O
its B-CON
by O
Wei B-PER
L I-PER
J I-PER

is O
there O
any O
researcher O

2027 B-DATE
Chan B-PER
Tak-Hang I-PER
's O
interact B-CON
works O
which O
is O
related O
to O
Henan B-KEY
Province I-KEY
written O
at O
1923 B-DATE

what O
are O
ethylene B-KEY
professor O

search O
computer B-KEY
graphics I-KEY
Mirvish B-PER
Sidney I-PER
S I-PER
's O
1920 B-DATE
paper O
written O
in O
1906 B-DATE

Takubo B-PER
, I-PER
T I-PER
. I-PER
's O
JP B-ORG
Morgan I-ORG
aggregation B-KEY
researches O
appearing O
on O
percom B-CON
which O
are O
by O
Rui B-PER
Kuang I-PER

search O
the O
list O
of O
Coursera B-ORG
2018 B-DATE
anor B-CON
researches O
published O
on O
misq B-CON
on O
density B-KEY
functional I-KEY
theory I-KEY

which O
are O
isi B-CON
2002 B-DATE
papers O
received O
by O
apsec B-CON
written O
by O
Zhang B-PER
Ya-Nan I-PER
from O
Merrimack B-ORG
College I-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wisconsin-Madison I-ORG
- I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Business I-ORG
nerve B-KEY
growth I-KEY
factor I-KEY
publications O
focusing O
on O
cyanobacteria B-KEY
appearing O
on O
bmvc B-CON
made O
by O
Bridgewater B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG

Iravani B-PER
J I-PER
robocup B-CON
publications O
which O
is O
published O
in O
1997 B-DATE
about O
Sleep B-KEY

Weber B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
monet B-CON
researches O
which O
is O
at O
1954 B-DATE
that O
is O
made O
by O
Boeing B-ORG

Stanley B-PER
Klein I-PER
's O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
at I-ORG
Boulder I-ORG
cvgip B-CON
journals O
related O
to O
HIV/AIDS B-KEY
published O
by O
Friedman B-PER
Norman I-PER
R I-PER
done O
by O
Colby B-ORG
College I-ORG

what O
is O
Trinity B-ORG
College I-ORG
, I-ORG
Dublin I-ORG
scientists O
that O
have O
conducted O
research O
on O
Dulbecco B-KEY
's I-KEY
modified I-KEY
Eagle I-KEY
's I-KEY
medium I-KEY
at O
EXPRESS B-ORG

is O
there O
any O
sodium B-KEY
conference O
on O
circular B-KEY
dichroism I-KEY

differential B-KEY
scanning I-KEY
calorimetry I-KEY
simpra B-CON
works O
on O
stacs B-CON
done O
by O
Joyce B-PER
C I-PER
W I-PER
that O
are O
by O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Padova I-ORG

sigcomm B-CON
Winthrop B-ORG
University I-ORG
2004 B-DATE
desorption B-KEY
papers O
done O
at O
1927 B-DATE
published O
on O
ton B-CON

Fuhrman B-PER
F I-PER
A I-PER
wetice B-CON
works O
done O
by O
T. B-PER
Kirchhoff I-PER
appearing O
on O
ita B-CON
published O
by O
self B-ORG
employed I-ORG

Prudential B-ORG
Financial I-ORG
MEMS B-KEY
experts O
at O
CB B-ORG
Richard I-ORG
Ellis I-ORG

Ferris B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
experts O
doing O
research O
on O
Nanowires B-KEY
at O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leuven I-ORG

is O
there O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
at I-ORG
Denver I-ORG
experts O
who O
have O
conducted O
research O
on O
flow B-KEY
field I-KEY
working O
at O
Saudi B-ORG
Aramco I-ORG

look O
up O
for O
the O
group O
of O
Nieboer B-PER
Anna I-PER
Petra I-PER
protease B-KEY
1902 B-DATE
publications O
from O
UCLA B-ORG
Anderson I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Management I-ORG
made O
by O
Sillat B-PER
Tarvo I-PER

search O
1973 B-DATE
europar B-CON
publications O
on O
optimization B-KEY
done O
by O
Bowling B-ORG
Green I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
that O
is O
written O
by O
Ahdieh B-PER
M I-PER
done O
in O
1957 B-DATE

expert O
that O
work O
in O
Durham B-ORG
University I-ORG

find O
some O
siggraph B-CON
Dongo B-PER
E I-PER
's O
Fudan B-ORG
University I-ORG
work O
that O
are O
done O
in O
1930 B-DATE

are O
there O
any O
ijis B-CON
Universitat B-ORG
de I-ORG
València I-ORG
1987 B-DATE
publication O
appearing O
on O
issre B-CON
which O
is O
by O
Davenport B-ORG
University I-ORG
that O
is O
made O
at O
1979 B-DATE

are O
there O
jscic B-CON
Phase B-KEY
separation I-KEY
1971 B-DATE
research O
made O
in O
2015 B-DATE

journals O

what O
are O
matrix B-KEY
Benedictine B-ORG
University I-ORG
professor O
that O
is O
in O
Reply B-ORG

conceptual B-KEY
model I-KEY
journals O
of O
which O
the O
paper O
focus O
on O
Coronary B-KEY
disease I-KEY

experts O
conducting O
research O
on O
formal B-KEY
specification I-KEY

fish B-KEY
conference O

which O
is O
John B-PER
Aldo I-PER
Lee I-PER
1923 B-DATE
TiO2 B-KEY
Bayer B-ORG
HealthCare I-ORG
researches O
from O
Colditz B-PER
I I-PER
G I-PER
accepted O
by O
jsyml B-CON
related O
to O
steel B-KEY
structure I-KEY
written O
at O
2000 B-DATE
written O
by O
UCSD B-ORG

are O
there O
any O
1991 B-DATE
jifs B-CON
Samuel B-PER
Hawgood I-PER
work O
made O
by O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Manchester I-ORG
done O
at O
1966 B-DATE

are O
there O
any O
1913 B-DATE
Lizard-Nacol B-PER
Sarab I-PER
's O
journals O
by O
Thompson B-PER
H I-PER
S I-PER
done O
by O
Duke B-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
appearing O
on O
apsipa B-CON
done O
in O
2001 B-DATE
that O
is O
related O
to O
antibacterial B-KEY

sLogica B-CON
yield B-KEY
Fiorina B-PER
Paolo I-PER
Shanghai B-ORG
Jiao I-ORG
Tong I-ORG
University I-ORG
publication O
related O
to O
X-ray B-KEY
photoelectron I-KEY
spectroscopy I-KEY
appearing O
on O
jim B-CON
made O
by O
DE B-PER
BIASIO I-PER
B I-PER

ESADE B-ORG
Business I-ORG
& I-ORG
Law I-ORG
School I-ORG
1981 B-DATE
Kavanaugh B-PER
K I-PER
M I-PER
publications O
that O
is O
done O
in O
2000 B-DATE
made O
by O
Kent B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
which O
is O
about O
high B-KEY
level I-KEY

give O
me O
Rolls B-PER
Edmund I-PER
T I-PER
1963 B-DATE
work O
about O
lubrication B-KEY
by O
Wang B-PER
Xunzhang I-PER
written O
by O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Auckland I-ORG
published O
at O
1904 B-DATE

which O
is O
percutaneous B-KEY
coronary I-KEY
intervention I-KEY
journal O

are O
there O
any O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Iowa I-ORG
experts O
working O
on O
index B-KEY
in O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Missouri-Saint I-ORG
Louis I-ORG

conference O

look O
up O
for O
higher B-KEY
vocational I-KEY
colleges I-KEY
Lomonosov B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
( I-ORG
MSU I-ORG
) I-ORG
professor O
whose O
research O
focus O
on O
thinking B-KEY

search O
conference O
on O
knowledge-based B-KEY
system I-KEY

conference O
about O
peroxidase B-KEY

Nortel B-ORG
Networks I-ORG
mitochondrial B-KEY
dna I-KEY
researcher O
doing O
Nucleation B-KEY
from O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Texas I-ORG
at I-ORG
Dallas I-ORG

dyeing B-KEY
B B-PER
Parry I-PER
researches O
focusing O
on O
logic B-KEY
published O
at O
1900 B-DATE
published O
by O
Cahen B-PER
P I-PER
written O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wisconsin-Stout I-ORG

research O
written O
by O
Beton B-PER
focusing O
on O
Aging B-KEY
received O
by O
hci B-CON

search O
for O
a O
list O
of O
experts O
working O
at O
Red B-ORG
Bull I-ORG

Dai B-PER
Feng I-PER
iwcmc B-CON
1992 B-DATE
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Portsmouth I-ORG
journal O
written O
by O
De B-PER
Beer I-PER
Thomas I-PER
appearing O
on O
nla B-CON

wan O
na O
find O
Thäder B-PER
J I-PER
's O
work O
done O
by O
Inditex B-ORG
written O
at O
2013 B-DATE

Bournemouth B-ORG
University I-ORG
expert O
from O
William B-ORG
Paterson I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
Jersey I-ORG

are O
there O
any O
expert O
in O
Politecnico B-ORG
di I-ORG
Milano I-ORG

PWM B-KEY
conferences O
related O
to O
Nanoparticles B-KEY

give O
me O
professors O

Igaki B-PER
Hiroyasu I-PER
's O
Université B-ORG
Laval I-ORG
spl B-CON
extraction B-KEY
papers O
written O
by O
Ewald B-PER
F I-PER
C I-PER
made O
at O
1914 B-DATE
on O
taslp B-CON

Bissoli B-PER
L I-PER
's O
1990 B-DATE
journals O
that O
is O
by O
Digital B-ORG
Equipment I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG

Vassar B-ORG
College I-ORG
scientists O

find O
for O
ABN B-ORG
AMRO I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
N.V I-ORG
. I-ORG
papers O
written O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Helsinki I-ORG
that O
is O
published O
at O
2011 B-DATE

are O
there O
any O
parameter B-KEY
optimization I-KEY
experts O
at O
GE B-ORG
Aviation I-ORG

search O
for O
GAUTIER B-PER
1983 B-DATE
journal O
appearing O
in O
isscc B-CON
made O
by O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Postal I-ORG
Service I-ORG
about O
Phosphorylation B-KEY
made O
by O
McQuade B-PER
T I-PER
J I-PER

find O
for O
incentives B-KEY
experts O

want O
to O
find O
Capgemini B-ORG
Consulting I-ORG
morbidity B-KEY
mie B-CON
publication O
from O
Oxford B-ORG
University I-ORG
Press I-ORG
from O
Russell B-PER
Jason I-PER
D I-PER
on O
sucrose B-KEY
which O
is O
in O
1909 B-DATE

J.P. B-ORG
Morgan I-ORG
flocculation B-KEY
expert O
that O
is O
in O
Qualcomm B-ORG

are O
there O
conferences O

experts O
working O
on O
time B-KEY
series I-KEY
analysis I-KEY
at O
Columbia B-ORG
College I-ORG
Chicago I-ORG

what O
is O
inflation B-KEY
experts O

query O
ijhci B-CON
substantia B-KEY
nigra I-KEY
Kaiser B-ORG
Permanente I-ORG
research O
published O
by O
Harman B-PER
Everett I-PER
A I-PER
done O
in O
1900 B-DATE
appearing O
on O
tit B-CON
made O
by O
Marsh B-ORG

2002 B-DATE
General B-ORG
Assembly I-ORG
water B-KEY
use I-KEY
efficiency I-KEY
research O
appearing O
on O
geoinformatics B-CON

what O
are O
zeolite B-KEY
Sony B-ORG
D'Souza B-PER
Deepak I-PER
Cyril I-PER
's O
publications O

Complement B-KEY
paper O
that O
are O
received O
by O
tsp B-CON
which O
is O
related O
to O
Holocene B-KEY

find O
for O
ESSEC B-ORG
Business I-ORG
School I-ORG
professor O
working O
at O
Technion B-ORG
- I-ORG
Israel I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
vascular B-KEY

everis B-ORG
scientists O

what O
are O
Roche B-ORG
Pharmaceuticals I-ORG
works O
received O
by O
cssc B-CON

are O
there O
any O
American B-ORG
Express I-ORG
expert O

endm B-CON
protein B-KEY
works O
that O
is O
received O
by O
jasss B-CON

people O

find O
a O
list O
of O
Mercy B-ORG
College I-ORG
1993 B-DATE
nitrate B-KEY
researches O
written O
at O
1910 B-DATE
that O
are O
published O
by O
PNC B-ORG

Ya-Ping B-PER
Wang I-PER
2027 B-DATE
Verizon B-ORG
papers O
that O
are O
written O
at O
1927 B-DATE
published O
on O
logcom B-CON

what O
are O
journal O

researchers O

expert O

search O
inducible B-KEY
nitric I-KEY
oxide I-KEY
synthase I-KEY
conference O
that O
is O
related O
to O
geographic B-KEY
information I-KEY
system I-KEY

Carleton B-ORG
University I-ORG
Dervin B-PER
E I-PER
XPS B-KEY
1918 B-DATE
works O
written O
by O
Rutgers B-ORG
University I-ORG
related O
to O
habitat B-KEY
that O
are O
written O
by O
Cheung B-PER
B I-PER

hydrothermal B-KEY
synthesis I-KEY
scientist O
who O
work O
at O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California I-ORG
, I-ORG
Santa I-ORG
Barbara I-ORG

Young B-ORG
& I-ORG
Rubicam I-ORG
paper O
that O
are O
related O
to O
Rheology B-KEY
that O
is O
written O
at O
1965 B-DATE

U.S. B-ORG
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Representatives I-ORG
HDL B-KEY
Naiqing B-PER
Ye I-PER
2026 B-DATE
siamjo B-CON
publications O
done O
in O
1944 B-DATE
written O
by O
Ikebe B-PER
R I-PER
which O
are O
published O
by O
Freescale B-ORG
Semiconductor I-ORG

are O
there O
storage B-KEY
papers O
done O
in O
1990 B-DATE
made O
by O
ConAgra B-ORG
Foods I-ORG
made O
by O
Cross B-PER
T I-PER

are O
there O
journal O

course B-KEY
Pratt B-ORG
& I-ORG
Whitney I-ORG
expert O
doing O
research O
on O
nature B-KEY

scientists O
conducting O
research O
on O
Etiology B-KEY

query O
the O
ccr B-CON
paper O
done O
by O
Webster B-ORG
University I-ORG

National B-ORG
University I-ORG
Groen B-PER
Henk I-PER
journals O
that O
is O
done O
in O
1982 B-DATE
from O
CNN B-ORG
on O
selection B-KEY

who O
is O
scientists O
in O
Huawei B-ORG

query O
1934 B-DATE
researches O
appearing O
on O
asc B-CON

is O
there O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Edinburgh I-ORG
explosion B-KEY
scientist O
in O
Citigroup B-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
chaos B-KEY

want O
to O
find O
the O
group O
of O
Kotchoni B-PER
Simeon I-PER
O I-PER
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Rochester I-ORG
icalt B-CON
1965 B-DATE
journals O
made O
by O
Avery B-ORG
Dennison I-ORG
done O
in O
2000 B-DATE

look O
up O
for O
ets B-CON
infertility B-KEY
researches O
received O
by O
cscw B-CON
made O
by O
Lasky B-PER
I I-PER
I I-PER
about O
Neutrophil B-KEY
that O
is O
written O
in O
1991 B-DATE
made O
by O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Santiago I-ORG
de I-ORG
Compostela I-ORG

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Pacific I-ORG
scientist O
that O
work O
in O
Queens B-ORG
College I-ORG

are O
there O
protein B-KEY
kinase I-KEY
A I-KEY
Fusco B-PER
Giuseppe I-PER
journal O
on O
informs B-CON
that O
is O
about O
Monte B-KEY
Carlo I-KEY
simulation I-KEY

formal B-KEY
verification I-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Exeter I-ORG
professor O
working O
at O
Pace B-ORG
University I-ORG

conferences O

what O
are O
data B-KEY
stream I-KEY
expert O
from O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
University I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG

education B-KEY
researchers O
in O
Pontificia B-ORG
Universidad I-ORG
Católica I-ORG
de I-ORG
Chile I-ORG
working O
on O
smooth B-KEY

CA B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
iasam B-CON
Aoyagi B-PER
T I-PER
's O
1952 B-DATE
mitochondrial B-KEY
dna I-KEY
paper O
which O
are O
written O
by O
Tulane B-ORG
University I-ORG

genetic B-KEY
diversity I-KEY
journals O
on O
which O
the O
paper O
is O
in O
commercial B-KEY
bank I-KEY

chemical B-KEY
constituents I-KEY
scientists O
conducting O
research O
on O
siRNA B-KEY

are O
there O
Debat B-PER
Vincent I-PER
architectural B-KEY
design I-KEY
work O
that O
are O
by O
salesforce.com B-ORG
published O
at O
2016 B-DATE
which O
is O
accepted O
by O
tvlsi B-CON

Diamond B-KEY
papers O
on O
inspection B-KEY
in O
1971 B-DATE

what O
is O
journals O
related O
to O
surgery B-KEY

Valeo B-ORG
professor O
from O
Massachusetts B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
who O
is O
doing O
research O
on O
status B-KEY
quo I-KEY

CAM B-KEY
expert O
working O
on O
fingerprint B-KEY

DEA B-KEY
journal O
whose O
papers O
is O
in O
forest B-KEY

objective B-KEY
function I-KEY
conference O
on O
rehabilitation B-KEY

Furth B-PER
M I-PER
E I-PER
1973 B-DATE
paper O
published O
by O
Chi B-PER
E I-PER
done O
by O
Peking B-ORG
University I-ORG
that O
is O
made O
at O
1948 B-DATE

give O
me O
Metals B-KEY
people O
in O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Hong I-ORG
Kong I-ORG
whose O
papers O
focus O
on O
Schizophrenia B-KEY

are O
there O
electrophoresis B-KEY
scientists O

wan O
na O
find O
the O
list O
of O
experimental B-KEY
result I-KEY
professor O
who O
is O
doing O
research O
on O
cyclic B-KEY
AMP I-KEY
in O
Sun B-ORG
Yat-Sen I-ORG
University I-ORG

Peace B-ORG
Corps I-ORG
professor O

give O
me O
some O
Robert B-ORG
Half I-ORG
International I-ORG
middleware B-KEY
1931 B-DATE
publication O
at O
1919 B-DATE
from O
UPS B-ORG

scientist O
whose O
papers O
are O
about O
PWM B-KEY

are O
there O
1947 B-DATE
publications O
done O
by O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
at I-ORG
Binghamton I-ORG
written O
in O
2022 B-DATE

renewable B-KEY
energy I-KEY
experts O

wan O
na O
find O
professors O

are O
there O
any O
1993 B-DATE
works O
written O
by O
Henkel B-ORG

2029 B-DATE
heat B-KEY
treatment I-KEY
tit B-CON
researches O
received O
by O
iconip B-CON
from O
Reid B-PER
U I-PER
V I-PER

what O
are O
School B-ORG
name I-ORG
: I-ORG
professors O
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Detroit I-ORG
Mercy I-ORG

which O
are O
prostate B-KEY
journal O
on O
coordination B-KEY

journal O

what O
are O
literature B-KEY
review I-KEY
islped B-CON
T. B-PER
Shikama I-PER
's O
1937 B-DATE
research O
which O
are O
from O
Melnick B-PER
D I-PER
in O
1968 B-DATE
received O
by O
jet B-CON

conferences O
related O
to O
quality B-KEY
management I-KEY

system B-KEY
model I-KEY
SAS B-ORG
researcher O
working O
on O
existing B-KEY
method I-KEY

what O
is O
journal O
which O
is O
about O
prototype B-KEY
system I-KEY

scientist O
whose O
paper O
is O
in O
research B-KEY

intrusion B-KEY
detection I-KEY
system I-KEY
publication O
which O
is O
received O
by O
fuzzIEEE B-CON
from O
UC B-ORG
Berkeley I-ORG

wan O
na O
find O
some O
researcher O
who O
are O
in O
Davenport B-ORG
University I-ORG

what O
are O
conferences O
about O
important B-KEY
issue I-KEY

pik B-CON
Carpenter B-PER
Z I-PER
L I-PER
's O
dynamic B-KEY
characteristics I-KEY
research O
published O
by O
Atos B-ORG

acidity B-KEY
ConocoPhillips B-ORG
scientist O
doing O
mechanism B-KEY

conference O

Adecco B-ORG
Group I-ORG
1912 B-DATE
Yoo B-PER
Kyung I-PER
Soo I-PER
research O
that O
is O
about O
curriculum B-KEY
reform I-KEY
accepted O
by O
geb B-CON

2029 B-DATE
papers O
done O
by O
Elzevier B-PER
H I-PER
W I-PER
accepted O
by O
icsoc B-CON

which O
is O
N. B-PER
Santamaria I-PER
titb B-CON
Bath B-ORG
& I-ORG
Body I-ORG
Works I-ORG
work O
which O
are O
related O
to O
representation B-KEY

find O
ESADE B-ORG
Business I-ORG
School I-ORG
researchers O
doing O
image B-KEY
processing I-KEY
that O
is O
in O
ANZ B-ORG

is O
there O
any O
graph B-KEY
work O
related O
to O
SDS B-KEY
by O
Qiuping B-PER
Hu I-PER
made O
at O
2023 B-DATE

find O
conferences O
that O
is O
about O
X-ray B-KEY
computed I-KEY

which O
is O
Histamine B-KEY
journals O
about O
Scanning B-KEY
tunneling I-KEY
microscopy I-KEY

who O
are O
NHS B-ORG
scientist O
conducting O
research O
on O
Cytochrome B-KEY
c I-KEY
at O
Universidad B-ORG
Autónoma I-ORG
de I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG

City B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
City I-ORG
College I-ORG
incentives B-KEY
publications O
appearing O
on O
hipc B-CON

which O
is O
RadioShack B-ORG
cluster B-CON
researches O
which O
is O
from O
USAA B-ORG
that O
are O
about O
benign B-KEY
prostatic I-KEY
hyperplasia I-KEY
from O
Daher B-PER
Wassim I-PER

are O
there O
Universidade B-ORG
Estadual I-ORG
de I-ORG
Campinas I-ORG
Diangui B-PER
Huang I-PER
maturity B-KEY
work O
that O
focus O
on O
P2P B-KEY

look O
up O
for O
Casado B-PER
Santiago I-PER
2015 B-DATE
Xi'an B-ORG
Jiaotong I-ORG
University I-ORG
paper O
appearing O
on O
jsyml B-CON

United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Marine I-ORG
Corps I-ORG
expert O
who O
is O
expert O
at O
Molecular B-KEY
modeling I-KEY
from O
Excelsior B-ORG
College I-ORG

Apple B-ORG
2008 B-DATE
researches O

is O
there O
any O
professors O
doing O
expert B-KEY
system I-KEY

what O
is O
professor O
at O
Jadavpur B-ORG
University I-ORG

Mars B-ORG
people O
whose O
researches O
is O
about O
personality B-KEY

2012 B-DATE
Laurent B-PER
J I-PER
M I-PER
M B-ORG
& I-ORG
T I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
work O
published O
on O
sigcse B-CON

is O
there O
Reply B-ORG
analytical B-KEY
model I-KEY
esws B-CON
journal O
written O
at O
1929 B-DATE
on O
recognition B-KEY

is O
there O
any O
Zhang B-PER
Qiao I-PER
Nanoparticles B-KEY
publication O
focusing O
on O
Iron B-KEY
written O
at O
2029 B-DATE

want O
to O
find O
ammonia B-KEY
expert O
doing O
research O
on O
shear B-KEY
strength I-KEY

what O
is O
Laurence B-PER
Weiss I-PER
's O
accretion B-KEY
1909 B-DATE
journals O
that O
are O
made O
in O
1995 B-DATE
from O
Levinson B-PER
M I-PER
R I-PER
done O
by O
Pfizer B-ORG

are O
there O
any O
tac B-CON
researches O
written O
by O
Huaining B-PER
Wu I-PER
from O
Drake B-ORG
University I-ORG

who O
is O
scientist O

Oregon B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
Chan B-PER
K I-PER
F I-PER
1920 B-DATE
ett B-CON
MES B-KEY
publication O
by O
Cognizant B-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Solutions I-ORG
accepted O
by O
cisis B-CON

search O
for O
conference O

find O
for O
bootstrap B-KEY
Agostini B-PER
V I-PER
publications O
written O
by O
Université B-ORG
catholique I-ORG
de I-ORG
Louvain I-ORG
on O
equipment B-KEY
published O
by O
Lheureux B-PER
P I-PER

Differential B-KEY
diagnosis I-KEY
scientists O

1996 B-DATE
Streitberger B-PER
Kaspar-Josche I-PER
's O
publications O
which O
is O
made O
by O
University B-ORG
at I-ORG
Albany I-ORG
, I-ORG
SUNY I-ORG
that O
focus O
on O
ideology B-KEY
by O
Millman B-PER
S I-PER
T I-PER
which O
appear O
in O
dft B-CON

are O
there O
any O
Lystsov B-PER
V I-PER
N I-PER
cucumber B-KEY
2025 B-DATE
publications O
from O
Ca B-ORG
' I-ORG
Foscari I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Venice I-ORG
from O
Mizuno B-PER
Noriyoshi I-PER

R. B-PER
Oppenheim I-PER
's O
1975 B-DATE
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Detroit I-ORG
Mercy I-ORG
research O
from O
Dengming B-PER
Wang I-PER
which O
are O
related O
to O
endothelin B-KEY

find O
simpra B-CON
Chow B-PER
J I-PER
C I-PER
's O
1944 B-DATE
Trinity B-ORG
College-Hartford I-ORG
journals O
from O
Universidad B-ORG
Francisco I-ORG
de I-ORG
Vitoria I-ORG
written O
in O
2007 B-DATE
received O
by O
cars B-CON

relaxation B-KEY
conference O

which O
is O
logcom B-CON
Gold B-KEY
papers O
which O
is O
published O
by O
Jaw B-PER
T I-PER
S I-PER
published O
in O
1944 B-DATE
from O
Northeastern B-ORG
Illinois I-ORG
University I-ORG

module B-KEY
Fidelity B-ORG
Investments I-ORG
expert O
doing O
research O
on O
algorithm B-KEY

1923 B-DATE
emnlp B-CON
paper O
that O
are O
related O
to O
Titanium B-KEY
made O
by O
Dingle B-PER
K I-PER
E I-PER

find O
for O
laser B-KEY
technique I-KEY
journals O

are O
there O
Reinert B-PER
M I-PER
1948 B-DATE
Autoantibodies B-KEY
paper O
done O
by O
Chopra B-PER
Abha I-PER

Bittar B-PER
A I-PER
E I-PER
's O
1979 B-DATE
paper O
on O
drug B-KEY
therapy I-KEY
written O
in O
1919 B-DATE
made O
by O
Song B-PER
Min I-PER
Sup I-PER

look O
up O
for O
conferences O

2011 B-DATE
web B-KEY
server I-KEY
Lavoratore B-ORG
autonomo I-ORG
Cormier B-PER
J I-PER
M I-PER
ijcomsys B-CON
journals O
which O
are O
about O
PID B-KEY
control I-KEY
published O
by O
MIT B-ORG
appearing O
on O
orl B-CON

look O
up O
for O
the O
list O
of O
advertising B-KEY
conferences O
about O
injection B-KEY
molding I-KEY

want O
to O
find O
the O
list O
of O
publication O
received O
by O
dsn B-CON
focusing O
on O
interoperability B-KEY

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California I-ORG
, I-ORG
Berkeley I-ORG
, I-ORG
Haas I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Business I-ORG
Braverman B-PER
A I-PER
's O
scl B-CON
publication O
which O
is O
related O
to O
three-dimensional B-KEY
published O
on O
jfr B-CON
that O
is O
published O
in O
1958 B-DATE

search O
inhibition B-KEY
expert O
from O
Medtronic B-ORG
working O
on O
CNS B-KEY

query O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Miami I-ORG
- I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Business I-ORG
propagation B-KEY
scientists O
working O
at O
EXPRESS B-ORG

which O
is O
Radiation B-KEY
therapy I-KEY
isscc B-CON
Choraian B-PER
O I-PER
G I-PER
's O
work O
about O
information B-KEY
processing I-KEY
in O
2004 B-DATE
that O
is O
published O
by O
Johns B-ORG
Hopkins I-ORG
University I-ORG
done O
by O
LoGrasso B-PER
P I-PER
V I-PER

tumor B-KEY
necrosis I-KEY
factor-α I-KEY
Meierhenry B-PER
E I-PER
F I-PER
's O
bmvc B-CON
publication O
which O
are O
related O
to O
dynamics B-KEY
done O
by O
Peters B-PER
Bjoern I-PER

ram B-CON
1957 B-DATE
Sahrmann B-PER
Shirley I-PER
A I-PER
publication O
in O
2010 B-DATE
which O
appear O
on O
chinaf B-CON
related O
to O
eye B-KEY
movement I-KEY
that O
is O
done O
by O
Deutsche B-ORG
Bank I-ORG

toms B-CON
2008 B-DATE
Tanaka B-PER
Ryosuke I-PER
's O
researches O
done O
by O
Nicopoullos B-PER
James I-PER
D I-PER
M I-PER

give O
me O
CuiXia B-PER
Sheng I-PER
1946 B-DATE
experimental B-KEY
research I-KEY
research O
accepted O
by O
gecco B-CON

which O
are O
Kigure B-PER
T I-PER
's O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
of I-ORG
China I-ORG
transformation B-KEY
works O
focusing O
on O
multimedia B-KEY
application I-KEY

Newcomer B-PER
R I-PER
J I-PER
NBC B-ORG
Universal I-ORG
researches O
appearing O
on O
jss B-CON

want O
to O
find O
Université B-ORG
libre I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bruxelles I-ORG
edge B-KEY
detection I-KEY
experts O
from O
Adecco B-ORG

formal B-KEY
method I-KEY
Bunatian B-PER
A I-PER
F I-PER
's O
papers O
that O
are O
about O
upper B-KEY
bound I-KEY
made O
by O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Siena I-ORG
received O
by O
mipro B-CON
done O
in O
1962 B-DATE

are O
there O
any O
collagen B-KEY
researchers O
doing O
research O
on O
localization B-KEY

SSC B-KEY
General B-ORG
Assembly I-ORG
scientists O

journal O
on O
which O
the O
paper O
focus O
on O
fish B-KEY

search O
turkey B-KEY
journal O

is O
there O
any O
1949 B-DATE
antibacterial B-KEY
activity I-KEY
icdm B-CON
works O
from O
British B-ORG
Council I-ORG
that O
is O
published O
in O
1943 B-DATE

want O
to O
find O
journals O

which O
is O
Huber B-PER
Hans I-PER
E I-PER
's O
bmvc B-CON
symmetry B-KEY
IBM B-ORG
journals O
published O
on O
IEEEicci B-CON
made O
in O
1936 B-DATE

publication O
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aberdeen I-ORG
done O
by O
M B-PER
Jensen I-PER

show O
T. B-PER
Kotzer I-PER
's O
spe B-CON
1943 B-DATE
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Arkansas I-ORG
at I-ORG
Little I-ORG
Rock I-ORG
publications O
which O
are O
from O
E. B-PER
Buckley I-PER
about O
Incidence B-KEY
done O
at O
2016 B-DATE

OFDM B-KEY
journal O

Qualcomm B-ORG
Oxidative B-KEY
stress I-KEY
scientist O
doing O
principle B-KEY

search O
researchers O

which O
are O
coordination B-KEY
research O
which O
are O
made O
by O
Pálfi B-PER
György I-PER

conference O

what O
is O
professors O

libt B-CON
Sánchez-Casado B-PER
E I-PER
1967 B-DATE
works O
that O
is O
related O
to O
operating B-KEY
system I-KEY
written O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
South I-ORG
Florida I-ORG
that O
is O
on O
seke B-CON
which O
is O
made O
by O
Williams B-PER
Y I-PER

researchers O

which O
is O
broiler B-KEY
journal O
related O
to O
malondialdehyde B-KEY

is O
there O
scientist O

are O
there O
professors O
doing O
research O
on O
feedback B-KEY
at O
Utah B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG

is O
there O
conference O

Sony B-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
biological B-KEY
characteristics I-KEY
researcher O

are O
there O
feasibility B-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Leeds I-ORG
scientist O
in O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Nevada-Reno I-ORG

are O
there O
any O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Arizona I-ORG
1982 B-DATE
publication O
from O
Valeo B-ORG
made O
in O
2016 B-DATE
made O
by O
Schlitzkus B-PER
Lisa I-PER
L I-PER

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Kentucky I-ORG
researcher O
doing O
research O
on O
efficiency B-KEY

MATLAB B-KEY
Lewis B-ORG
University I-ORG
researches O
on O
cataract B-KEY
in O
1957 B-DATE
done O
by O
Mizerski B-PER
J I-PER

find O
for O
a O
list O
of O
conference O

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Surrey I-ORG
Bobitt B-PER
J I-PER
R I-PER
naacl B-CON
papers O
appearing O
on O
jirs B-CON

search O
for O
research O
on O
ultraviolet B-KEY
on O
eor B-CON
made O
at O
1923 B-DATE
published O
by O
Uddin B-PER
, I-PER
S I-PER
. I-PER

transplantation B-KEY
conferences O

journal O
focusing O
on O
animal B-KEY

1931 B-DATE
papers O
which O
is O
related O
to O
Research B-KEY
Articles I-KEY
which O
are O
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
San I-ORG
Diego I-ORG
that O
is O
made O
by O
Kelley B-PER
S I-PER
J I-PER
made O
at O
1975 B-DATE
appearing O
in O
icdcs B-CON

what O
are O
Sexual B-KEY
behavior I-KEY
wcsp B-CON
R. B-PER
Riding I-PER
's O
1916 B-DATE
Convergys B-ORG
works O
about O
G B-KEY
protein-coupled I-KEY
receptor I-KEY
appearing O
on O
icis B-CON
which O
is O
made O
by O
Nascimento B-PER
Sérgio I-PER
M I-PER
C I-PER

behavior B-KEY
researcher O
that O
is O
from O
Hamline B-ORG
University I-ORG
whose O
researches O
are O
in O
biodiversity B-KEY

what O
are O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Colorado I-ORG
Boulder I-ORG
paper O
focusing O
on O
potential B-KEY
by O
Sciences B-ORG
Po I-ORG
that O
is O
published O
on O
compsac B-CON
published O
in O
1954 B-DATE
done O
by O
Barr B-PER
Christina I-PER
S I-PER

what O
are O
researchers O
from O
Yale B-ORG
University I-ORG

Mast B-KEY
cell I-KEY
Southern B-ORG
Methodist I-ORG
University I-ORG
scientist O
doing O
data B-KEY
warehouse I-KEY
who O
are O
from O
Discover B-ORG
Financial I-ORG
Services I-ORG

give O
me O
inversion B-KEY
conference O
related O
to O
activated B-KEY
sludge I-KEY

find O
for O
conferences O

search O
2016 B-DATE
Kiessling B-PER
Anna I-PER
paper O
written O
by O
Banco B-ORG
Santander I-ORG
from O
Gruszecki B-PER
W I-PER
I I-PER
focusing O
on O
pragmatics B-KEY

Manning B-PER
A I-PER
P I-PER
1991 B-DATE
prl B-CON
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Florida I-ORG
paper O
received O
by O
date B-CON
by O
Sonoma B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
focusing O
on O
chicken B-KEY

is O
there O
gender B-KEY
dgo B-CON
researches O
in O
2010 B-DATE
focusing O
on O
Cell B-KEY
adhesion I-KEY
from O
Cameron B-ORG
made O
by O
Yulong B-PER
Guo I-PER

1996 B-DATE
Baudoux B-PER
E I-PER
's O
economics B-KEY
work O
which O
are O
from O
N. B-PER
Joshi I-PER
about O
improvement B-KEY
received O
by O
icalp B-CON
which O
is O
in O
1996 B-DATE

sensitivity B-KEY
analysis I-KEY
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Massachusetts I-ORG
Lowell I-ORG
people O

want O
to O
find O
reverse B-KEY
engineering I-KEY
Enterprise B-ORG
Rent-A-Car I-ORG
1998 B-DATE
researches O
written O
by O
Ubisoft B-ORG
on O
biogeography B-KEY

Antibiotics B-KEY
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Salford I-ORG
people O
whose O
works O
are O
in O
protein B-KEY
structure I-KEY

give O
me O
the O
list O
of O
sufficient B-KEY
condition I-KEY
scientists O

are O
there O
1941 B-DATE
Nehrir B-PER
, I-PER
M.H I-PER
. I-PER
's O
Kaiser B-ORG
Permanente I-ORG
publication O
published O
at O
1937 B-DATE
related O
to O
G B-KEY
protein I-KEY

search O
for O
works O
related O
to O
side B-KEY
effects I-KEY
appearing O
in O
popl B-CON
written O
by O
Fung B-PER
L I-PER
F I-PER
which O
is O
written O
in O
1908 B-DATE
made O
by O
Adecco B-ORG

Web B-KEY
conferences O
related O
to O
ventilation B-KEY

are O
there O
any O
Surface B-KEY
structure I-KEY
researchers O
that O
work O
at O
General B-ORG
Dynamics I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

object-oriented B-KEY
programming I-KEY
Darling B-PER
S I-PER
T I-PER
's O
1908 B-DATE
researches O
written O
by O
Likhachev B-PER
S I-PER
A I-PER
made O
by O
Lund B-ORG
University I-ORG

find O
for O
a O
group O
of O
error B-KEY
experts O
doing O
microsatellite B-KEY

Universidad B-ORG
Pontificia I-ORG
Comillas I-ORG
scientist O
doing O
research O
on O
modularization B-KEY

ijmmsc B-CON
Hawton B-PER
Keith I-PER
's O
papers O
related O
to O
compost B-KEY
published O
in O
1951 B-DATE
published O
by O
Yadi B-PER
Li I-PER
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Sussex I-ORG

scientists O
at O
Schlumberger B-ORG

1912 B-DATE
mam B-CON
researches O
made O
in O
1956 B-DATE

Carleton B-ORG
University I-ORG
experts O

researchers O

query O
the O
group O
of O
ROSEN B-PER
F I-PER
S I-PER
1901 B-DATE
papers O
that O
is O
written O
by O
Visa B-ORG

search O
for O
Bank B-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
tim B-CON
distribution B-KEY
works O
on O
ram B-CON
on O
Malaria B-KEY

want O
to O
find O
those O
mtDNA B-KEY
papers O
that O
is O
published O
on O
comcom B-CON

experimental B-KEY
evaluation I-KEY
conferences O

who O
is O
scientists O
whose O
work O
is O
about O
Colorectal B-KEY
neoplasms I-KEY

are O
there O
any O
conference O

ERP B-KEY
scientists O
in O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Ottawa I-ORG

computer B-KEY
system I-KEY
conference O
focusing O
on O
brain B-KEY
injury I-KEY

internet B-KEY
scientist O
from O
Barclays B-ORG
Bank I-ORG

find O
for O
Fibrosis B-KEY
professors O
that O
is O
doing O
constitutive B-KEY
model I-KEY

Ethier B-PER
S I-PER
P I-PER
's O
Crystal B-KEY
growth I-KEY
work O
written O
at O
2006 B-DATE
by O
Inglis B-PER
Diane I-PER
O I-PER

PayPal B-ORG
professors O
at O
Peace B-ORG
Corps I-ORG

1951 B-DATE
researches O
published O
in O
1919 B-DATE
done O
by O
Nortel B-ORG

which O
are O
Yongling B-PER
Yu I-PER
's O
postmodernism B-KEY
tim B-CON
1973 B-DATE
publications O
that O
is O
done O
by O
Davidson B-PER
Michael I-PER
W I-PER
on O
calculation B-KEY
written O
at O
1902 B-DATE
which O
are O
received O
by O
pvm B-CON

who O
are O
professors O
who O
are O
doing O
research O
on O
near B-KEY
infrared I-KEY
spectroscopy I-KEY

Davidson B-PER
Harriet I-PER
J I-PER
Atorvastatin B-KEY
journal O
about O
ion B-KEY
exchange I-KEY
which O
are O
published O
by O
Qazi B-PER
Ghulam I-PER
N I-PER
written O
at O
1976 B-DATE

The B-ORG
Manchester I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
University I-ORG
English B-KEY
teaching I-KEY
expert O
in O
Rhode B-ORG
Island I-ORG
College I-ORG

Towers B-ORG
Watson I-ORG
scientists O
in O
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Bari I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
MODIS B-KEY

look O
up O
for O
contamination B-KEY
Emmelkamp B-PER
Paul I-PER
M I-PER
G I-PER
's O
interactions B-CON
1960 B-DATE
works O
from O
Fei B-PER
Jiang I-PER
from O
Middlesex B-ORG
University I-ORG

Kennesaw B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
1914 B-DATE
paper O
published O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
South I-ORG
Australia I-ORG
published O
in O
1957 B-DATE
focusing O
on O
COPD B-KEY
done O
by O
Vanessa B-PER
Evers I-PER

1949 B-DATE
Rudich B-PER
Steven I-PER
M I-PER
publication O
which O
is O
made O
by O
Barry B-PER
T I-PER
N I-PER
received O
by O
ijmms B-CON
which O
is O
done O
in O
1904 B-DATE

give O
me O
intrusion B-KEY
detection I-KEY
system I-KEY
professor O
whose O
research O
is O
in O
PEG B-KEY

which O
is O
conferences O
which O
is O
about O
dimethyl B-KEY
sulfoxide I-KEY

congestive B-KEY
heart I-KEY
failure I-KEY
professors O
whose O
research O
are O
about O
testis B-KEY

show O
Honeywell B-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
data B-KEY
transmission I-KEY
scientists O

material B-KEY
1949 B-DATE
Philip B-ORG
Morris I-ORG
International I-ORG
ijar B-CON
H. B-PER
Larsson I-PER
publications O
published O
on O
pcm B-CON
which O
is O
related O
to O
three-dimensional B-KEY

look O
up O
for O
a O
group O
of O
control B-KEY
system I-KEY
journals O

want O
to O
find O
people O

SanDisk B-ORG
brand B-KEY
Joel B-PER
Cooper I-PER
trec B-CON
publication O
about O
approximation B-KEY
algorithm I-KEY
which O
are O
written O
by O
M. B-PER
Zwahlen I-PER

scientist O
whose O
work O
is O
related O
to O
virtual B-KEY
prototype I-KEY
at O
Indiana B-ORG
University I-ORG

Aon B-ORG
Hewitt I-ORG
Microscopy B-KEY
crypto B-CON
works O
published O
on O
csur B-CON

are O
there O
accv B-CON
1940 B-DATE
journals O
from O
K B-PER
GOTO I-PER
in O
1914 B-DATE
focusing O
on O
non-small B-KEY
cell I-KEY
lung I-KEY
cancer I-KEY

is O
there O
any O
industrialization B-KEY
journals O
which O
are O
about O
JNK B-KEY

1976 B-DATE
works O
which O
is O
written O
at O
1922 B-DATE

find O
the O
1904 B-DATE
researches O
from O
Fuzhi B-PER
Wang I-PER
accepted O
by O
ecir B-CON
about O
chitosan B-KEY

query O
journals O
related O
to O
active B-KEY
learning I-KEY

find O
for O
expert O

want O
to O
find O
people O
doing O
variation B-KEY

search O
for O
Williams B-ORG
College I-ORG
professors O
conducting O
research O
on O
women B-KEY
working O
at O
Huawei B-ORG

experts O
that O
are O
from O
The B-ORG
Citadel I-ORG

accretion B-KEY
expert O
at O
Schneider B-ORG
Electric I-ORG

what O
are O
conference O
of O
which O
the O
papers O
are O
in O
body B-KEY
weight I-KEY

show O
college B-KEY
students I-KEY
researchers O
doing O
regeneration B-KEY
from O
IKEA B-ORG
Group I-ORG

icppw B-CON
García B-PER
Laraña I-PER
J I-PER
HCA B-ORG
papers O
accepted O
by O
fpga B-CON
that O
is O
about O
N B-KEY
-2-hydroxyethylpiperazine- I-KEY
N I-KEY
′-2-ethanesulfonic I-KEY
acid I-KEY

is O
there O
1949 B-DATE
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Hartford I-ORG
work O
about O
parallel B-KEY
computing I-KEY
which O
are O
done O
by O
California B-ORG
State I-ORG
University-Sacramento I-ORG
made O
by O
D B-PER
Hess I-PER
published O
on O
jco B-CON

are O
there O
scientists O
from O
Adobe B-ORG

what O
is O
goat B-KEY
1927 B-DATE
uai B-CON
journal O
by O
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Castilla-La I-ORG
Mancha I-ORG
on O
recycling B-KEY
appearing O
on O
mor B-CON
which O
is O
made O
at O
2016 B-DATE

find O
1976 B-DATE
journals O
which O
are O
related O
to O
seed B-KEY
written O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Southern I-ORG
Maine I-ORG
done O
by O
Hot B-PER
David I-PER

what O
is O
Mehta B-PER
Anand I-PER
Universidad B-ORG
de I-ORG
Valladolid I-ORG
paper O
appearing O
in O
tkde B-CON
that O
are O
by O
Colman B-PER
Robert I-PER
W I-PER
published O
in O
2023 B-DATE

search O
Aalborg B-ORG
Universitet I-ORG
system B-KEY
integration I-KEY
researchers O

interleukin B-KEY
experts O
from O
Utah B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
who O
have O
been O
working O
on O
progress B-KEY

are O
there O
any O
wcsp B-CON
24 B-ORG
Hour I-ORG
Fitness I-ORG
1939 B-DATE
publications O
that O
is O
in O
1941 B-DATE
focusing O
on O
calibration B-KEY
which O
is O
received O
by O
bibe B-CON

wan O
na O
find O
advertising B-KEY
scientists O
whose O
work O
is O
related O
to O
threshold B-KEY

give O
me O
dam B-CON
K B-PER
ZAGHLOUL I-PER
's O
1936 B-DATE
researches O
made O
in O
1919 B-DATE
received O
by O
icassp B-CON
from O
Georgia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

Viacom B-ORG
Biosensor B-KEY
professor O
doing O
financing B-KEY

find O
Sciences B-ORG
Po I-ORG
scientist O
conducting O
research O
on O
contamination B-KEY
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
London I-ORG

polyethylene B-KEY
Northrop B-ORG
Grumman I-ORG
work O

1933 B-DATE
jnca B-CON
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Sussex I-ORG
paper O
done O
by O
Rosanio B-PER
S I-PER
on O
particle B-KEY
filter I-KEY
which O
are O
in O
1937 B-DATE

give O
me O
the O
1934 B-DATE
Ludwig-Maximilians B-ORG
Universität I-ORG
München I-ORG
publication O
done O
in O
1959 B-DATE
that O
are O
by O
Cheng B-PER
Ning I-PER
appearing O
on O
ibmrd B-CON

researchers O

behaviourIT B-CON
Heiba B-PER
Sherif I-PER
's O
journals O
on O
trust B-KEY
which O
are O
on O
kybernetes B-CON

are O
there O
any O
higher B-KEY
education I-KEY
journal O

query O
Indesit B-ORG
Company I-ORG
professor O
at O
Pfizer B-ORG
Pharmaceuticals I-ORG

researches O
which O
is O
related O
to O
fuzzy B-KEY
system I-KEY
done O
by O
Texas B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG

which O
are O
conferences O

Convergys B-ORG
professor O
conducting O
research O
on O
software B-KEY
design I-KEY

1927 B-DATE
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
San I-ORG
Francisco I-ORG
publication O
about O
hip B-KEY
published O
by O
Lenucci B-PER
Marcello I-PER
S I-PER
appearing O
in O
ibmsj B-CON
that O
is O
done O
at O
1940 B-DATE

query O
conference O

find O
a O
list O
of O
compare B-KEY
professors O
in O
British B-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
doing O
blood B-KEY
glucose I-KEY

want O
to O
find O
Monte B-KEY
Carlo I-KEY
conferences O
about O
formation B-KEY

query O
Microsoft B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
growth B-KEY
and I-KEY
development I-KEY
expert O
who O
are O
from O
East B-ORG
China I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
University I-ORG
whose O
paper O
is O
related O
to O
authorization B-KEY

give O
me O
vlsid B-CON
Landesberg B-PER
Amir I-PER
Brandeis B-ORG
University I-ORG
work O
that O
are O
published O
by O
Bank B-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
by O
Güneri B-PER
Tamer I-PER
published O
in O
2016 B-DATE

give O
me O
coagulation B-KEY
professors O
doing O
esterification B-KEY

coco B-CON
Wenxuan B-PER
Ge I-PER
's O
1956 B-DATE
probiotics B-KEY
Harvard B-ORG
Medical I-ORG
School I-ORG
publications O
about O
Marx B-KEY

journals O

people O
whose O
papers O
are O
in O
chaos B-KEY

who O
are O
fuzzy B-KEY
comprehensive I-KEY
evaluation I-KEY
expert O
working O
on O
orthogonal B-KEY
design I-KEY

who O
are O
phosphatidylcholine B-KEY
professor O
from O
Washington B-ORG
and I-ORG
Lee I-ORG
University I-ORG
who O
have O
conducted O
research O
on O
Europe B-KEY

are O
there O
1939 B-DATE
works O
published O
by O
The B-ORG
Boeing I-ORG
Company I-ORG
on O
jmlr B-CON

wan O
na O
find O
Nonomura B-PER
N I-PER
's O
influence B-KEY
Eli B-ORG
Lilly I-ORG
and I-ORG
Company I-ORG
work O
that O
are O
accepted O
by O
tbc B-CON

professors O
who O
are O
experts O
at O
magnesium B-KEY

linear B-KEY
system I-KEY
people O

vulnerability B-KEY
conferences O

search O
Dixon B-PER
C I-PER
M I-PER
icee B-CON
Smith B-ORG
College I-ORG
publication O
from O
Talbot B-PER
I I-PER
C I-PER

is O
there O
its B-CON
analytical B-KEY
method I-KEY
2015 B-DATE
Siemens B-ORG
Healthcare I-ORG
publications O
made O
at O
1913 B-DATE
related O
to O
JNK B-KEY

NCR B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
Paul B-PER
H I-PER
A I-PER
's O
publication O
on O
ERP B-KEY
which O
is O
in O
1983 B-DATE
published O
by O
Yahoo B-ORG

is O
there O
Toys B-ORG
R I-ORG
Us I-ORG
professors O
from O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Memphis I-ORG
doing O
research O
on O
fatty B-KEY
acids I-KEY

find O
conference O

search O
for O
scientist O
whose O
works O
is O
in O
service B-KEY
composition I-KEY

what O
are O
system B-KEY
identification I-KEY
Walden B-ORG
University I-ORG
researcher O

fault B-KEY
conferences O

what O
are O
DSC B-KEY
journals O
focusing O
on O
internal B-KEY

1959 B-DATE
Richard B-PER
Eckersley I-PER
cviu B-CON
researches O
at O
1988 B-DATE
on O
finite B-KEY
difference I-KEY
method I-KEY

BHP B-ORG
Billiton I-ORG
efficiency B-KEY
professors O
from O
The B-ORG
George I-ORG
Washington I-ORG
University I-ORG
- I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Business I-ORG

Universidad B-ORG
Antonio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Nebrija I-ORG
object B-KEY
recognition I-KEY
experts O

2007 B-DATE
system B-KEY
performance I-KEY
paper O
on O
FBS B-KEY
written O
by O
Zhejiang B-ORG
University I-ORG
accepted O
by O
telsys B-CON

Yahong B-PER
Li I-PER
publications O
from O
G. B-PER
Stover I-PER
related O
to O
esterification B-KEY
made O
at O
1961 B-DATE

panel B-KEY
data I-KEY
conferences O

researches O
on O
distribution B-KEY
network I-KEY
published O
by O
Xi'an B-ORG
Jiaotong I-ORG
University I-ORG

conferences O
focusing O
on O
Irradiation B-KEY

object B-KEY
journal O

fuzzIEEE B-CON
1915 B-DATE
Jingyu B-PER
Liang I-PER
publications O
which O
appear O
on O
annals B-CON
done O
by O
Universidad B-ORG
Pontificia I-ORG
de I-ORG
Salamanca I-ORG
that O
is O
about O
zinc B-KEY

want O
to O
find O
vegetation B-KEY
scientist O

BlackBerry B-ORG
researchers O
working O
at O
Procter B-ORG
& I-ORG
Gamble I-ORG
working O
on O
India B-KEY

is O
there O
any O
novel B-KEY
method I-KEY
scientists O
who O
do O
maize B-KEY
working O
at O
Indiana B-ORG
University I-ORG

Owusu-Ofori B-PER
Shirley I-PER
ESADE B-ORG
Business I-ORG
& I-ORG
Law I-ORG
School I-ORG
paper O
by O
Harris B-PER
Julie I-PER
M I-PER

side B-KEY
effects I-KEY
Hewitt B-ORG
Associates I-ORG
experts O
doing O
mechanical B-KEY
properties I-KEY

what O
are O
Lin B-PER
James I-PER
C I-PER
's O
orthogonal B-KEY
design I-KEY
fsttcs B-CON
Wipro B-ORG
researches O
published O
by O
Koroleva B-PER
L I-PER
S I-PER
done O
by O
State B-ORG
Street I-ORG

Seneca B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
expert O

what O
is O
journal O

irrigation B-KEY
people O
doing O
Titanium B-KEY

Austin B-ORG
Community I-ORG
College I-ORG
scientist O
working O
at O
Comverse B-ORG
whose O
researches O
focus O
on O
management B-KEY
system I-KEY

Universiteit B-ORG
Utrecht I-ORG
experts O
from O
Aetna B-ORG

give O
me O
St. B-ORG
Olaf I-ORG
College I-ORG
jkm B-CON
journal O
written O
in O
1972 B-DATE
appearing O
on O
mcs B-CON

search O
a O
list O
of O
scientists O
who O
are O
from O
Rowan B-ORG
University I-ORG

conference O

1941 B-DATE
graph B-KEY
works O
on O
competition B-KEY
from O
Klimenko B-PER
E I-PER
D I-PER
done O
by O
American B-ORG
Red I-ORG
Cross I-ORG

Seneca B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
researcher O
at O
California B-ORG
State I-ORG
University-Long I-ORG
Beach I-ORG

show O
N B-KEY
-2-hydroxyethylpiperazine- I-KEY
N I-KEY
′-2-ethanesulfonic I-KEY
acid I-KEY
journal O
that O
focus O
on O
data B-KEY
structure I-KEY

what O
are O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
St. I-ORG
Thomas I-ORG
expert O
in O
Apple B-ORG
doing O
database B-KEY
system I-KEY

Georgia B-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
professor O
working O
on O
dynamic B-KEY
model I-KEY

journal O
focusing O
on O
ecological B-KEY
environment I-KEY

assets B-CON
1972 B-DATE
CONDITIONING B-KEY
Than B-PER
Manuel I-PER
E I-PER
papers O
accepted O
by O
jcc B-CON
made O
at O
1987 B-DATE

are O
there O
Fluorescence B-KEY
journals O

Bombardier B-ORG
Transportation I-ORG
1918 B-DATE
EGFR B-KEY
papers O
accepted O
by O
technometrics B-CON
which O
are O
by O
Old B-ORG
Dominion I-ORG
University I-ORG

people O

find O
journal O

Huawei B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
expert O
conducting O
research O
on O
biomechanics B-KEY

University B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
Haven I-ORG
scientist O
at O
Discover B-ORG
Financial I-ORG
Services I-ORG

Rutgers B-ORG
, I-ORG
The I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
Jersey-New I-ORG
Brunswick I-ORG
iiwas B-CON
Jolepalem B-PER
Prashant I-PER
Subarachnoid B-KEY
hemorrhage I-KEY
1996 B-DATE
research O
from O
Harrison B-PER
C I-PER
N I-PER
about O
object-oriented B-KEY
that O
are O
made O
at O
1966 B-DATE

which O
is O
Erythrocyte B-KEY
conference O

Lipid B-KEY
peroxidation I-KEY
researcher O
at O
Eastern B-ORG
Michigan I-ORG
University I-ORG
conducting O
research O
on O
fault B-KEY
diagnosis I-KEY

Schaub B-PER
A I-PER
's O
1981 B-DATE
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Wollongong I-ORG
Surveillance B-KEY
work O
published O
by O
Corbascio B-PER
M I-PER
which O
is O
related O
to O
Helicobacter B-KEY
pylori I-KEY
published O
in O
1976 B-DATE

journals O
on O
forecast B-KEY

cutting B-KEY
conference O

query O
the O
list O
of O
accumulation B-KEY
American B-ORG
Express I-ORG
journal O
focusing O
on O
FITC B-KEY
that O
are O
made O
by O
Queen B-ORG
's I-ORG
University I-ORG

researcher O

find O
for O
journal O
done O
in O
1956 B-DATE
which O
are O
from O
TCS B-ORG
which O
are O
by O
Prasad B-PER
Abhishek I-PER

look O
up O
for O
a O
group O
of O
journals O

show O
journals O
about O
quality B-KEY
assurance I-KEY

journals O

what O
is O
genetic B-KEY
programming I-KEY
1941 B-DATE
algorithmica B-CON
Infosys B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
Ltd I-ORG
works O
on O
Morphine B-KEY
that O
are O
done O
by O
Macy B-ORG
's I-ORG

want O
to O
find O
growth B-KEY
and I-KEY
development I-KEY
1950 B-DATE
icc B-CON
Ting B-PER
Feng I-PER
's O
publication O
which O
is O
made O
at O
1966 B-DATE
which O
are O
received O
by O
icde B-CON

Ecole B-ORG
polytechnique I-ORG
professors O
from O
GE B-ORG
Capital I-ORG
whose O
works O
are O
about O
Protein B-KEY
kinase I-KEY

A. B-PER
Vos I-PER
's O
journals O
that O
are O
at O
1903 B-DATE
appearing O
on O
iui B-CON
about O
enlightenment B-KEY

conformation B-KEY
experts O
that O
are O
in O
Lloyds B-ORG
Banking I-ORG
Group I-ORG
that O
are O
experts O
at O
Endothelium B-KEY

1934 B-DATE
cma B-CON
City B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York-Hunter I-ORG
College I-ORG
papers O
that O
focus O
on O
reliability B-KEY
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Toledo I-ORG
accepted O
by O
cogsci B-CON

are O
there O
any O
experts O
working O
on O
ontology B-KEY

Comcast B-ORG
Cable I-ORG
professor O
conducting O
research O
on O
business B-KEY
process I-KEY

Valdés B-PER
Chávarri I-PER
M I-PER
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Louisiana I-ORG
at I-ORG
Lafayette I-ORG
1904 B-DATE
journals O
on O
bioinformatics B-CON
done O
in O
1982 B-DATE

what O
is O
expert O

is O
there O
any O
Dartmouth B-ORG
College I-ORG
magnetic B-KEY
resonance I-KEY
experts O
working O
at O
Agilent B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG

find O
conflict B-KEY
Paychex B-ORG
researchers O
in O
Obama B-ORG
for I-ORG
America I-ORG

conferences O
on O
Acupuncture B-KEY

smc B-CON
Università B-ORG
degli I-ORG
Studi I-ORG
di I-ORG
Palermo I-ORG
stress B-KEY
analysis I-KEY
journals O
published O
in O
1922 B-DATE

is O
there O
any O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Military I-ORG
Academy I-ORG
at I-ORG
West I-ORG
Point I-ORG
Neuroscience B-KEY
expert O
conducting O
research O
on O
remote B-KEY
monitoring I-KEY
who O
is O
from O
Xerox B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG

give O
me O
journals O

search O
a O
group O
of O
papers O
by O
Wexler B-PER
David I-PER
received O
by O
geoinformatics B-CON

target B-KEY
researcher O
conducting O
research O
on O
Acupuncture B-KEY

is O
there O
any O
particle B-KEY
filter I-KEY
conferences O
whose O
papers O
are O
about O
bioactivity B-KEY

which O
is O
Sato B-PER
Osamu I-PER
's O
Excel B-KEY
High B-ORG
School I-ORG
itcc B-CON
journals O
accepted O
by O
jirs B-CON
on O
leadership B-KEY
from O
Thomas B-ORG
Edison I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG

is O
there O
any O
durability B-KEY
conferences O
focusing O
on O
design B-KEY
methodology I-KEY

bifurcation B-KEY
conference O

National B-ORG
Cheng I-ORG
Kung I-ORG
University I-ORG
Menif B-PER
Emna I-PER
's O
paper O
published O
at O
1940 B-DATE
which O
are O
done O
by O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Central I-ORG
Oklahoma I-ORG

look O
up O
for O
people-oriented B-KEY
conference O

Yu B-PER
Y I-PER
Z I-PER
's O
research O
done O
at O
1957 B-DATE
related O
to O
Confucianism B-KEY
received O
by O
mansci B-CON

is O
there O
kais B-CON
papers O
written O
in O
1923 B-DATE
by O
Yongyang B-PER
Zhang I-PER

show O
Universitat B-ORG
Autònoma I-ORG
de I-ORG
Barcelona I-ORG
scientists O
who O
have O
been O
working O
on O
way B-KEY

Endoscopy B-KEY
journal O
published O
on O
cikm B-CON
done O
by O
The B-ORG
Ritz-Carlton I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
Company I-ORG
LLC I-ORG
which O
is O
made O
in O
1987 B-DATE
that O
is O
about O
socialism B-KEY
that O
is O
by O
Yueling B-PER
Huang I-PER

search O
for O
1947 B-DATE
work O
written O
by O
US B-ORG
Navy I-ORG
done O
at O
1985 B-DATE
written O
by O
C. B-PER
Schulman I-PER
on O
high-density B-KEY
lipoprotein I-KEY

high B-KEY
performance I-KEY
icdcs B-CON
journal O
that O
is O
on O
hpdc B-CON
done O
by O
Iida B-PER
, I-PER
K I-PER
. I-PER
related O
to O
people-oriented B-KEY
written O
in O
1913 B-DATE

economy B-KEY
journals O
about O
natural B-KEY
language I-KEY
processing I-KEY

MAPK B-KEY
conferences O
related O
to O
coordination B-KEY

what O
are O
professor O
doing O
research O
on O
Nursing B-KEY
care I-KEY

are O
there O
test B-KEY
case I-KEY
people O
working O
at O
Belmont B-ORG
University I-ORG
that O
is O
doing O
urinary B-KEY
tract I-KEY
infection I-KEY

ppsn B-CON
1961 B-DATE
Drexel B-ORG
University I-ORG
Haak B-PER
H I-PER
L I-PER
's O
publication O
published O
in O
2028 B-DATE
which O
are O
published O
by O
Express B-ORG
Scripts I-ORG
accepted O
by O
iccnc B-CON
